[{"value": {"id": 1858826, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her Pakistani counterparts concerning the detention of Asif Pervaiz; and what diplomatic steps she is taking to support his release.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the Hon. Member to the answer given on 12 June to question 58220.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asif Pervaiz", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858826", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858824, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96037", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to ensure that bus service planning by local authorities considers the needs of older people who can no longer drive.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["96036"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government knows that bus services can be a lifeline for many in rural areas and can be the only means of accessing essential services. Action is being taken to help improve local bus services across the country through the Bus Services Act 2025 whic...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "96036", "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858824", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858823, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the number of older people in rural areas who rely solely on bus services for travel.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["96037"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government knows that bus services can be a lifeline for many in rural areas and can be the only means of accessing essential services. Action is being taken to help improve local bus services across the country through the Bus Services Act 2025 whic...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "96037", "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858823", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858632, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95805", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many visas the Electoral Commission have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 1560, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Electoral Commission has not sponsored any visas since 4 July 2024.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electoral Commission: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858632", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860151, "askingMemberId": 5244, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has discussions planned with nature organisations including the Woodland Trust, Wildlife Trusts and Wildlife and Countryside Link on potential secondary legislation ar", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860150, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to lay Great British Railways\u2019 draft and final Integrated Business Plans before Parliament for scrutiny.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860141, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97081", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has considered providing temporary relief from CO2 compliance costs for UK refineries, in the context of two of the six UK refineries closing.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860140, "askingMemberId": 5244, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "97080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she has plans to implement the RSPB's Action Plan for Curlew published April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860138, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions her Department has had with the Welsh government regarding the drafting of the Railways Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860137, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any future uplift in the settlement requirement for English will apply to those on the BN(O) visa route.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860133, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "97077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of progress against the commitment in the NHS 10 Year Plan for Health to launch a new large-scale study to sequence the genomes of 150,000 adults and assess how g", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860126, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the proposed changes to English language requirements for Indefinite Leave to Remain applies to those on the BN(O) route.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860124, "askingMemberId": 5281, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to reduce delays in Access to Work applications; and if he will take steps to introduce a fast-track process for disability groups with the lowest employment rates, s", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860123, "askingMemberId": 5281, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will introduce mandatory disability pay gap reporting.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860122, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has he made of the potential benefits of increasing eligibility for free Covid vaccines to people with Respiratory Syncytial Virus.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860121, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has he made of the potential benefits of increasing eligibility for free Covid vaccines to people with Respiratory Syncytial Virus in West Dorset constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860120, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will extend the eligibility for free Covid vaccines to people with Respiratory Syncytial Virus.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860119, "askingMemberId": 4850, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97070", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the \u00a314.5 million for Grangemouth announced at the Budget relates to the previous commitment from the Prime Minister that \u00a3200 million from the National Wealth Fund would support the transition of the Grangemout", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860118, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will extend the eligibility for free Covid vaccines to people with Respiratory Syncytial Virus in West Dorset constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860117, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has had discussions with the BBC on managing conflicts of interest at BBC Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860115, "askingMemberId": 4850, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97067", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the expected breakdown of the \u00a314.5 million allocated to Grangemouth, including funding for site remediation, feasibility work, infrastructure upgrades, skills programmes, and any oth", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860114, "askingMemberId": 5268, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent conversations he has had with the Indian Government on the release of Jagtar Singh Johal from detention.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860113, "askingMemberId": 4850, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97065", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the \u00a314.5 million announced for Grangemouth at the November 2025 Budget will be allocated; and what project milestones or conditions must be met before funds are released.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860112, "askingMemberId": 5325, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what action the Government is taking to help ensure civilians who need to leave Gaza for urgent medical treatment are able to be evacuated.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860111, "askingMemberId": 5325, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what action the Government is taking to ensure sufficient humanitarian aid is entering Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860110, "askingMemberId": 5325, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what action the Government is taking to press for international journalists to be allowed into Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860108, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97061", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations she has received from airport operators regarding the potential impact of business rates changes announced in the Budget on the competitiveness of UK airports.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860107, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97060", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of increased aviation taxes on levels of inbound tourism to the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860106, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97059", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the revenues generated from the ending of free allowances under the UK Emissions Trading Scheme for aviation; and whether she plans to allocate those revenues to support the production ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860105, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97058", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact on families of increases in Air Passenger Duty for Premium Economy passengers announced in the Budget.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860104, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on what dates the industry working group established to support development of the local media strategy has met to date, and what the planned timescale is for its next meeting.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860103, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the Public Notice Portal\u2019s contribution to improving public engagement with statutory notices, and how its archive and consultation functions will be in", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860102, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the planned timescales are for the commencement of the statutory notices review.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860101, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97054", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the number and type of businesses that will be impacted by business rates relief changes announced in the Budget 2025 in (a) Bedfordshire, (b) the East of England and (c) t", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860100, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when his Department plans to publish the consultation on the technical detail of the new small parcels regulatory arrangements.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860099, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97052", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions Single Living Accommodation units in each UK local authority area have experienced loss of (a) heating and (b) hot water for over 24 hours in each year since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860098, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to improve cross-government understanding of developments in drone technology, and what plans the has to improve inter-departmental collaboration on ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860097, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97050", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what transparency, reporting and accounting requirements will be placed on the Office of Rail and Road to undertake effective monitoring and competition oversight of GBR\u2019s retail activities.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860096, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97049", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many complaints regarding (a) gas, (b) electrical and (c) water issues have been recorded in Single Living Accommodation in each UK local authority area in each year since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860095, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97048", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Single Living Accommodation units in each UK local authority area have recorded Legionella, in each year since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860081, "askingMemberId": 5264, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to limit the purchase of new-build properties by foreign investors.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860079, "askingMemberId": 5264, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to limit the number of long-term empty homes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860076, "askingMemberId": 4850, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97045", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date the National Wealth Fund Board was informed of the Government\u2019s intention to allocate \u00a3200 million to Grangemouth community; and whether the Board formally approved any such commitment in accordance wit", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860068, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to help ensure that less potable water is used for non-potable purposes.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860065, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97043", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households where (a) Pension Credit and (b) Housing Benefit is claimed receive additional consideration due to there being a polygamous marriage.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860063, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Family Court system, particularly in cases where one parent is legally represented and the other is not.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860062, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what is the total annual cost of legal aid issued in cases where one party subsequently (a) breaches court orders, (b) refuses contact arrangements and (c) obstructs proceedings.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860061, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what mechanisms exist to coordinate information between criminal courts and family courts.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860060, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of delays in the family courts caused by litigants in person on (a) one and (b) both sides of a case.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860056, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many litigants in person report that they were unable to present their case properly due to lack of representation in each of the last five years; and what assessment he has made of the effect on judicial out", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860044, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97037", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of family court cases did only one party receiving legal aid in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860040, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the financial equitableness when only one parent receives legal aid in family court proceedings.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860039, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the average financial cost for people meeting their own legal fees in family court proceedings in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860038, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97034", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the average amount repaid by people who had received legal aid in family court cases in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860036, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the average cost per case to the public purse of providing legal aid in family proceedings for which the latest data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860035, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many family court cases the mother acted as a litigant in person due to lack of access to (a) legal aid and (b) representation in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860034, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many family court cases the father acted as a litigant in person due to lack of access to (a) legal aid and (b) representation in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860032, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for legal aid in family proceedings were granted to fathers in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860031, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97029", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2025 to Question 91862 on the Marine Environment, what is the scope of the Sustainable Ocean Plan; what is the (a) process and (b) timetable for c", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860029, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of applications for legal aid in family proceedings have been granted to mothers in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860021, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the oral Answer of 20 November 2025, Official Report, Column 834, on Motorists, and further to the point of order of 25 November 2025, Official report, Column 261, on what date was she first aware o", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860012, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97026", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will make it her policy to support paid leave for fertility appointments.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860011, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, who has responsibility for preventing the availability of products containing Melanotan II in England; and what steps he has taken to tackle the availability of these products.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860010, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Cancer Plan will specifically address the availability of products containing Melanotan II.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860009, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, to set out the legal status of products containing Melanotan II, including i) tan-enhancing injections; ii) tan-enhancing nasal sprays; iii) other products the Department is aware of.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860006, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on software licenses from Microsoft in the last 12 months; and what proportion this represents of his Department\u2019s total technology spend.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860002, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how much his Department has spent on software licences from Microsoft in the last 12 months; and what proportion this represents of his Department\u2019s total technology spend.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860000, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much her Department has spent on software licences from Microsoft in the last 12 months; and what proportion this represents of her Department\u2019s total technology spend.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859998, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97019", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment she has made of the value achieved through recent contract negotiations with Microsoft; and what assurances are in place regarding future pricing.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859997, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97018", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on software licences from Microsoft in the last 12 months; and what proportion this represents of his Department\u2019s total technology spend.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859995, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2025 to Question 93242 on Military Alliances: Space, what is included under the banner of space services.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859994, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97016", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using scanning machines in probation offices to detect weapons; and what steps he is taking to ensure the safety of probation officers in the workplace.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859993, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of uniform changes proposed in the Children and Wellbeing Bill on parents who wish to buy branded uniform items for convenience.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859992, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97014", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date did Project Matcha (a) start and (b) end.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859991, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97013", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has sought assurances from the BBC on how it is ensuring that individuals with a history of antisemitic statements do not appear on (a) BBC Arabic and (b) other BBC channels.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859990, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97012", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the BBC's procedures for (a) identifying and (b) addressing antisemitic (i) content and (ii) tropes in its programming.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859989, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97011", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, whether the Attorney General has had recent discussions with his Cabinet colleagues on the Tobacco and Vapes Bill\u2019s legal compatibility with the Windsor Framework in relation to Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859988, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the growth in the availability of open source Chinese AI platforms on the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859983, "askingMemberId": 5120, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2025 to Question 92292, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the requirement for pre-visit notifications on the uptake of free ey", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859982, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "97008", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of SEND tribunal waiting times on the ability of families to hold local authorities to account for non-provision of SEND support.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859980, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "97007", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2025 to Question 94102 on Bathing Water (Amendment) (England and Wales) Regulations 2025, if she can outline the (a) local and (b) national stakeh", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859979, "askingMemberId": 5120, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason the independent review into civil unrest in Leicester in 2022 has not yet been published.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859978, "askingMemberId": 5120, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "97005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when his Department will publish the findings from the independent review into civil unrest in Leicester in 2022, commissioned in 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859977, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to utilise electronic health records indicating familial genetic predisposition to improve risk identification for men at increased risk of prostate cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859976, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "97003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of improving systems to identify men with (a) BRCA1 and (b) BRCA2 gene variations who may be eligible for prostate cancer screening.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859975, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "97002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of deforestation regulations under the Environment Act 2021 on smallholder farmers; and what steps the Government is taking to ensu", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859973, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "97001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the impact of leaving the EU single market on graduate employment opportunities.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859971, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "97000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether the Gigabit Broadband Voucher Scheme will be reintroduced in Henley and Thame constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859946, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-17T00:00:00", "uin": "96999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing the same protections to historic villages as is provided to historic towns in the National Planning Policy Fram", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859939, "askingMemberId": 5244, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "96998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of whether chalk streams are an irreplaceable habitat.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859938, "askingMemberId": 5244, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "96997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to add chalk streams to the National Planning Policy Framework as an irreplaceable habitat.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859937, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96996", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many specialist Parkinson\u2019s nurses are employed in the NHS in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859936, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many consultant geriatricians in England have specialist training in Parkinson\u2019s disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859935, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96994", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many consultant neurologists in England have specialist training in Parkinson\u2019s disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859933, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96993", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of people who had visas sponsored by Jhoots Group who had those visas (a) transferred and (b) renewed to Allied Pharmacies in the last six months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859932, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of people who had visas sponsored by Jhoots Group who had those visas renewed by Jhoots Group.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859930, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96991", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to (a) the report of the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman on communication of changes to women\u2019s State Pension age and (b) the Work and Pensions Committee\u2019s recommendations of May 2024 on compensation fo", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859929, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the consistency of pupil experience between Key Stage 1 and Key Stage 2; and what steps she is taking to address declines in pupil motivation or engagement during the transition ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859928, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with school governing bodies on improving transparency for parents.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859927, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "96988", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of local authority compliance with the national legislation establishing the threshold of (a) 10 sessions of unauthorised absence and (b) a rolling 10-school-week period for ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859926, "askingMemberId": 5172, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96987", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for local pedestrian safety of encouraging local authorities to prioritise the creation and connectivity of active travel routes in ways that could aff", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859924, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the Minimum Income Requirement to ensure that retired British citizens with substantial savings and no recourse to public funds are not prevented from living in the UK with their sp", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859921, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential severity of winter pressures on the NHS during winter 2025-2026.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859920, "askingMemberId": 5274, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people who suffer from severe gambling addiction receive prompt treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859919, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has provided to Neighbourhood Health Centre sites on integrating specialist neurology services with neighbourhood-based care teams.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859918, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96982", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of Neighbourhood Health Centre sites have prioritised neurology within their (a) initial service plans and (b) delivery models.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859917, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to require local authorities to collect and publish baseline data on current (a) sports facilities and (b) heritage landscapes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859916, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96980", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that the removal of a defendant's right to elect a jury trail is compatible with Article 6 of the ECHR.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859915, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of changes to the right to jury trial on the number of appeals and judicial review applications.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859914, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what data relating to local sports infrastructure her Department holds; and whether she holds datasets on local authority breakdowns.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859913, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 2 December 2025, what safeguards will be put in place to ensure that, where defendants can no longer elect a jury trial, decisions are (a) consistent and (b)", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859912, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of removing the right to elect for a jury trial on perceptions of the justice system of a) victims, b) witnesses and c) defendants.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859911, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of removing a defendant\u2019s right to choose trial by jury for certain offences on the constitution.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859909, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of removing a defendant\u2019s right to elect trial by jury for triable-either-way offences on public confidence in the criminal justice system.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859908, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding allocations have been made to local authorities for the protection and improvement of (a) sports pitches and (b) heritage landscapes since 4 July 2024; and if she will publish a brea", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859907, "askingMemberId": 5104, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96972", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that switchovers of legacy technology, such as digital terrestrial television, support uptake and inclusion amongst digitally excluded citizens.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859905, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) registered parks, (b) gardens and (c) designed landscapes are currently classed as at risk in each local authority.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859904, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96970", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish the most recent data held by her Department on the number of registered parks and gardens within each local authority area.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859903, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patients awaiting elective surgery are provided with clear and timely information about their position on waiting lists; and whether his Departmen", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859902, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of planning applications affecting sports pitches over the last five years by local authority.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859900, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the (a) distribution and (b) availability of sports pitches by local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859899, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96966", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what data her Department holds on the (i) number, (ii) type, and (ii) condition of publicly accessible sports pitches in each local authority area in England; and if she will publish that data.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859898, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has conducted an assessment of the potential impact of the UK-USA pharmaceutical deal on frontline NHS services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859897, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96964", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many complaints his Department has received in each of the last five years regarding DNR notices being applied without consent.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859896, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) families and (b) attorneys holding Power of Attorney are notified immediately when a DNR notice is added to a vulnerable adult\u2019s medical record.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859895, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure SEND is taken into account in school attendance\u00a0policies.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859894, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96961", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether guidance has been issued to NHS Trusts to ensure that DNR decisions are never made solely on the basis of disability, learning disability and special needs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859893, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England audits the use of DNR notices in cases involving vulnerable adults.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859892, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how he plans to fund the UK-US pharmaceutical deal.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859891, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96958", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what is the financial breakdown for the Local Growth Fund, including capital and revenue split, for (a) Wales (b) Scotland (c) Northern Ireland and (d) England.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859881, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what his planned timeline is for rolling out the Connections Accelerator Service.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859881", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859880, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96956", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of Housing First interventions for people experiencing homelessness on (a) health outcomes and (b) costs to the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859880", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859879, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96955", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what measures his Department is taking to ensure people admitted to hospital while rough sleeping have somewhere secure to sleep upon discharge from hospital.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859879", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859878, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96954", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what measures his Department is taking to improve the access people experiencing homelessness have to health and social care services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859878", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859877, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96953", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many new enquiries were opened into child benefit claims which were suspended from claimants as a result of data-sharing between HMRC and the Home Office in the period 1st to 30th November 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859877", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859876, "askingMemberId": 5348, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to shorten the time between a child\u2019s SEND diagnosis and them receiving their Education, Health and Care Plan (EHCP) in Hertfordshire.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859876", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859874, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96951", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of enabling Credit Unions to offer Help to Save accounts.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859874", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859873, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96950", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she will take to measure the impact of the Financial Inclusion Strategy in supporting the credit union sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859873", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859872, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96949", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she will take to increase levels of investment into community finance organisations such as credit unions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859872", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859871, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96948", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to expand the use of community optometry services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859871", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859870, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96947", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to expand the use of optometry-led diagnostic and treatment pathways.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859870", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859869, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96946", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of implementing the recommendations of the report by the Association of Optometrists entitled Key Interventions to Transform Eye Care", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859869", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859868, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96945", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of steps taken by Integrated Care Boards to address regional inequalities in access to eye care services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859868", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859867, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96944", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of eye care services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859867", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859865, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96943", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the (a) Minor Eye Conditions Service and (b) Community Urgent Eyecare Service on (i) patient outcomes and (ii) unnecessary referra", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859865", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859864, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96942", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the (a) Minor Eye Conditions Service and (b) Community Urgent Eyecare Service.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859864", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859863, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96941", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the provision of a Minor Eye Conditions Service in every part of the country.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859863", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859862, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96940", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions she has had with HM Treasury on the potential merits of ringfencing funding received from fines levied on tech platforms by Ofcom under the Online Safety Act to fund sp", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859862", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859861, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Gloucester City Council's finances on local government reorganisation in Gloucestershire.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859861", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859860, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96938", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what funding her Department has committed to providing specialist support services for survivors of technology-facilitated abuse and online violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859860", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859859, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 02 December 2025 to Question 94590 on Railways: Season Tickets, what the cost of a standard-class annual rail season ticket from (a) Lostwithiel, (b) Bodmin Parkway, (c) Liskeard and (", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859859", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859858, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have undergone specialist technology-facilitated domestic abuse training in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859858", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859857, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of technology-facilitated abuse incidents reported to the police in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859857", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859856, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the forthcoming Violence Against Women and Girls strategy and its delivery plan will include (a) funding and (b) measures to address technology-facilitated domestic abuse.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859856", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859855, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on the number of ticket sales for season tickets from (a) Longbridge, (b) Northfield and (c) Kings Norton to (i) Birmingham stations, (ii) Redditch and (iii) Bromsgrove in ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859855", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859852, "askingMemberId": 4923, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96932", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the expected timetable is for the publication, parliamentary introduction, and enactment of a fully trans-inclusive ban on conversion therapy in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859852", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859851, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many building assessment certificate applications have been (a) made to the building safety regulator, (b) approved, (c) refused, and (d) yet to be determined.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859851", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859850, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96930", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what is the average cost incurred by accountable persons for time spent by the building safety regulator to determine and issue a decision on a building assessment certificate ap", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859850", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859849, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many large panel system buildings have been registered with the building safety regulator.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859849", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859848, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of trends in the number of building assessment certificate application refusals on the lending, mortgage and insur", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859848", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859847, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96927", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has had recent discussions with Anas Sarwar MSP on the higher rate of the Energy Profits Levy since 30 October 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859847", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859844, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what progress has been made in supporting democratic institutions and election integrity in countries receiving UK development assistance.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859844", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859843, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, What recent discussions his Department has had with partners to counter human trafficking and modern slavery in global supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859843", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859842, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96924", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps the Department is taking to promote media freedom and protect journalists in countries where press freedoms are under threat.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859842", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859841, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, What assessment has been made of the effectiveness of UK sanctions regimes in disrupting malign activity.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859841", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859840, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what support the Department is providing to international efforts to prevent and respond to sexual violence in conflict.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859840", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859839, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions have taken place with Commonwealth partners on strengthening trade and investment cooperation.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859839", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859838, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96920", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, What steps his Department is taking to help protect cultural heritage sites at risk from conflict or natural disaster.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859838", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859831, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96919", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of trends in the level of legal costs associated with lower value clinical negligence claims.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859831", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859830, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of implementing the recommendations in the National Audit Office\u2019s report entitled Costs of clinical negligence, published on 17 Octo", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859830", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859829, "askingMemberId": 5344, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with NHS Trusts and clinical directors on ensuring surgical trainees have adequate access to operating theatres.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859829", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859828, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the findings of David Lock KC\u2019s review into clinical negligence costs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859828", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859827, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what requirements exist for follow-up contact within 48 hours of discharge from inpatient mental health services; and what assessment he has made of the adequacy of NHS compliance with these requir", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859827", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859826, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help support Mid and South Essex Integrated Care Board to reduce the number of pathways waiting more than 52 weeks for treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859826", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859825, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to restore the 18-week referral-to-treatment standard at Mid and South Essex Integrated Care Board; and by what timeframe.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859825", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859824, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of trends in the proportion of patients treated within 18 weeks in Mid and South Essex Integrated Care Board facilities ov", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859824", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859823, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support the Mid and South Essex Integrated Care Board to reduce its pathways waiting list.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859823", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859822, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96910", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she collects data on the number and proportion of first-time buyers using the Mortgage Guarantee Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859822", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859821, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment has his Department made of the potential impact of employer National Insurance Contribution increases in the financial year 2025/2026 on a) the charity sector and b) neuroreh", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859821", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859820, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96908", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Mortgage Guarantee Scheme on the number of first-time buyers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859820", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859819, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the Government\u2019s upcoming Acquired Brain Injury Action Plan will improve data recording and data access relating to brain injury survivors.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859819", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859818, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of reporting mechanisms in capturing breaches of employment law among temporary and seasonal workers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859818", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859817, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96905", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what policy areas are in the scope of the upcoming acquired brain injury action plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859817", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859816, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96904", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what information his Department holds on the number of breaches of employment law there have been in each sector during seasonal recruitment periods in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859816", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859815, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96903", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department will publish the Acquired Brain Injury Action plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859815", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859814, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many visas a) his Department, b) the Medicines and Healthcare Regulatory Agency, c) the UK Health Security Agency, d) the Care Quality Commission, e) the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Auth", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859814", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859812, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96901", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to help prevent discrimination against women in digital spaces.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859812", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859811, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time taken by local authorities to repair a reported pothole was in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859811", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859810, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many local bus routes ceased operating in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859810", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859809, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many rail passenger journeys were made in Great Britain in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859809", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859808, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the (a) name, (b) job title, (c) annual remuneration, (d) time commitment and (e) expected end date is for each direct ministerial appointment in his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859808", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859807, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the number of potholes filled by local authorities in England in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859807", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859806, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96895", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 28 November 2025 to question 93149, whether RISE advisors will be dismissed if they do not meet the Programme-level Key Performance Indicators.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859806", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859805, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96894", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) name, (b) job title, (c) annual remuneration, (d) time commitment and (e) expected end date is for each direct ministerial appointment in her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859805", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859804, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96893", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 28 November 2025 to question 93149, if she will publish the Programme-level Key Performance Indicators for RISE advisors.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859804", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859802, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96892", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has carried out an impact assessment on removing (a) racehorse training yards and (b) racecourses from the Retail, Hospitality, and Leisure business rate relief scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859802", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859801, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96891", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason (a) racehorse training yards and (b) racecourses have been removed from the Retail, Hospitality, and Leisure business rate relief scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859801", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859799, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96890", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the cost of removing (a) racehorse training yards and (b) racecourses from the Retail, Hospitality, and Leisure business rate relief scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859799", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859796, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96889", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many visas a) her Department, b) the Vehicle Certification Agency, c) East-West Rail, d) National Highways, e) Network Rail, f) Trinity House, g) the Civil Aviation Authority and h) Crossrail International ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859796", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859793, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to launch the study to sequence the genomes of 150,000 adults.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859793", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859789, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96887", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with her Chinese counterpart on (a) student numbers and (b) research funding in the UK higher education sector.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859789", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859785, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96886", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessments his department has made of the predicted total cost of UK-US pharmaceutical deal on the NHS budget.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859785", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859784, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96885", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many foreign students have had their visas revoked because of nationality security concerns since 2015, broken down by (a) year, and (b) nationality.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859784", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859782, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96884", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many visas a) her Department, b) the Government Actuary's Department, c) the UK Debt Management Office, d) the National Wealth Fund, e) the Crown Estate, f) the Financial Conduct Authority, g) UK Government Inve", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859782", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859781, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many incidents of espionage have been identified in British universities since 2015, broken down by (a) year, and (b) nationality of identified suspects.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859781", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859775, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96882", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many visas a) his Department, b) the Pension Protection Fund, and c) the Office for Nuclear Regulation have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859775", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859764, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help rescue Melanie Watters and Janine Reid in Sri Lanka following Cyclone Ditwah.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859764", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859761, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96880", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve access to (a) affordable and (b) flexible childcare provision through childminders in (i) Surrey and (ii) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859761", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859760, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96879", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support the financial sustainability of childminding roles in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859760", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859759, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of variations in the availability of wider support services for children undergoing NHS treatment in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859758, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help improve consistency in NHS support for children with serious health needs in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859757, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions her Department has had with sporting bodies on strengthening (a) welfare and (b) safeguarding arrangements for women in non-professional sport in (i) Surrey and (ii) Surre", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859756, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to improve access to recovery support for women in grassroots sport in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859755, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of strengthening safety requirements for diesel generators located near residential buildings in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heat", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859754, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96873", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will set out the difference between (a) recovered unpaid taxes and (b) outstanding unpaid taxes in the period since July 2024 to date.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859753, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96872", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help support local authorities in (a) monitoring and (b) mitigating carbon monoxide risks in mixed-use residential areas in (a) Surrey and ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859752, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure local health services are prepared to respond to incidents of mass carbon monoxide exposure in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859751, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96870", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of HMRC's ability to collect unpaid taxes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859750, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help support the fire and rescue service to respond effectively to carbon monoxide incidents in (a) Surrey and (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859749, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of regulatory measures to prevent repeated water supply failures during winter in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constitue", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859748, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions her Department has had with water companies on contingency planning for (a) prolonged water loss or (b) low pressure during winter in (i) Surrey and (ii) Surrey", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859747, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96866", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of requiring water companies to improve operational preparedness for treatment works failures during winter 2025-26 in (", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859746, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96865", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the risk of large-scale water outages during periods of cold weather in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859745, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96864", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the resilience of household water supplies during winter 2025-26 in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859745", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859742, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96863", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions his Department has had with local authorities on the role of (a) parish councils and (b) community groups in managing public assets in (i) Surrey and (ii)", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859741, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96862", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what support his Department is providing to local authorities managing cultural venue refurbishment projects in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859740, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96861", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the time taken for construction at cultural venues on access to the arts in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859739, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions her Department has had with local councils on the future of (a) community arts and (b) cultural infrastructure in (i) Surrey and (ii) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859738, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support the resilience of (a) cultural and (b) community venues in (i) Surrey and (ii) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859732, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 2 December 2025 to question 94926 on Ajax Vehicles: Health and Safety, whether vehicles within the Ajax programme will be available for use prior to the a) conclusion and b) implementati", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859731, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96857", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 2 December 2025 to question 94926 on Ajax Vehicles: Health and Safety, when the review into the Ajax programme will a) start and b) conclude.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859730, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what is the full scope of the five point action plan to tackle release inaccuracy announced by him on 11 November 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859730", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859729, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96855", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff within the HM Prison & Probation Service reliant on visas for employment have been employed since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859728, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 1 December 2025 to question 94541 on Ministry of Defence: Asbestos, what the cost was of the 119 awards for mesothelioma.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859727, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the projected cost is of the abolition of NHS England, including staff redundancy packages, consultancy fees, administration and restructuring costs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859726, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96852", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies on funding SEND provision of the mainstream school spending per pupil on page 122 of the Office for Budget Responsibility\u2019s Economic F", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859725, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of funding the cost of SEND provision from RDEL allocations on local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859724, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96850", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of mitigating the financial risk of the removal of the statutory override from local authorities regarding the requirement to balance budgets in 2028.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859723, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the deadline is for the submission of a development consent application for a third runway at Heathrow Airport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859722, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96848", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the feasibility of new terminals for the proposed third runway at Heathrow Airport being built and operated in competition with those run by the airport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859721, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by what date she plans to complete the review into airport funding.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859720, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the (a) effectiveness, (b) value for money and (c) adequacy of (i) leadership and (ii) accountability of Sports England.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859719, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "96845", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to support wards receiving funding through the Pride in Place programme in a) Telford, b) West Midlands and c) England.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859718, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "96844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what plans his Department has to support wards receiving funding through the Pride in Place programme in a) Telford, b) West Midlands and c) England.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859717, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "96843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to support wards receiving funding through the Pride in Place programme in a) Telford, b) West Midlands and c) England.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859716, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "96842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to support wards receiving funding through the Pride in Place programme in (a) Telford, (b) West Midlands and (c) England.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859715, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96841", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an estimate of the impact of the pay per mile tax on electric vehicle usage in the Fylde constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859714, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96840", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an estimate of how many businesses in the Fylde constituency will be impacted by the pay per mile tax on electric and hybrid cars.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859713, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96839", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what engagement she undertook with the pub and hospitality sector ahead of the 2025 Budget, particularly in the context of Business Rates.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859695, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96838", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his comment given to British Forces Broadcasting Service following reporting of medical discharges relating to operating in Ajax vehicles that Medical discharges are not attributed to individual", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859690, "askingMemberId": 5280, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96837", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions the Government has had with Anas Sarwar MSP on the formulation of public policy.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859682, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with international counterparts on protecting the right of nations to self-determination.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859681, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will set out a timeline for bringing section 102 of the Levelling Up and Regeneration Act 2023 into force.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859679, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96834", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of business tax rises on physical activity levels.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859678, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96833", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of business tax rises on the physical activity sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859677, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96832", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the cumulative effect of (a) increasing betting duties on seaside arcades, (b) a nightly levy on hotel stays, (c) the abolition of Favoured Tax Regime for Furnished Holiday Lets, (d) ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859676, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96831", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October to Question 77717 on Betting: Excise Duties, if she will list relevant engagements with ministers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859675, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96830", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will have discussions with the police to establish a National Police Trust funded from money seized from the proceeds of crime.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859674, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96829", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2025 to Question 78837 on Rural Areas: Economic Situation, what assessment she has made of the difference between the increase in costs for horsera", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859673, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96828", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2025 to Question 84932 on Business and Tourism: Greater London, if she will make an assessment of the potential economic impact of organised protests on tourism an", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859672, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96827", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November, to Question 87899 on Delivery Services: Driving Licences, if she will (a) publish the letter referred to from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Local Transpor", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859671, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96826", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue was generated in 2023/2024 from business rates on hereditaments that are being used for the provision of (a) sport, leisure and facilities to visiting members of the public and (b) casinos, gambling", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859670, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the causes of the increase in Universal Credit claimants who are not required to work; and what steps he is taking to reduce the number of Universal Credit claimants who a", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860156, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police forces carry naloxone on the front line.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860155, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help increase uptake of the HPV vaccine.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860154, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department holds information on the number of resident doctors who, whilst on strike, work for another trust.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860153, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96821", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2025 to Question 93572, what steps he is taking to protect NHS staff from second hand vape.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860152, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96820", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of patients waited more than (a) 12, (b) 24, (c) 48 and (d) 60 hours at A&E at Lincoln County Hospital in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860149, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96819", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many One-Way Effectors will be delivered under Project Brakestop.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860148, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96818", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled UK \u201cbuilding the factories of the future\u201d as government launches next phase of new munitions and energetics factories, published on 19 November 2025, whet", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860147, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96817", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled UK \u201cbuilding the factories of the future\u201d as government launches next phase of new munitions and energetics factories, published on 19 November 2025, when", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860146, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the in service date for the One-Way Effector delivered under Project Brakestop.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860145, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96815", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there has been any delay to the delivery of Project Brakestop.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860144, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96814", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide a list of each company currently operating under Project Brakestop.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860143, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on delivering Project Brakestop.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860142, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2025 to Question 94242 on Ukraine: Peacekeeping Operations, whether he has authorised any changes to the readiness levels of the (a) British Army, (b) Royal Navy, (c) Royal Ai", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860139, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96811", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what definition of inclusive education her Department uses.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860136, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96810", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many disciplinary cases were concluded against civil servants in (a) the Department and (b) its agencies by (i) outcome and (ii) whether the primary allegation related to (A) performance and (B) co", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860135, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what the total cost was of (a) settlement agreements and (b) special severance payments made to departing staff in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860134, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96808", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many and what proportion of staff in each grade were rated in the top performance category in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860132, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96807", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many and what proportion of staff were promoted (a) in-grade and (b) to a higher grade in the last year broken down by (i) performance marking in the previous year and (ii) grade.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860131, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what the average number of working days lost to sickness absence per full-time equivalent member of staff was in (a) the Department and (b) its executive agencies in the last year; and how many formal ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860130, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96805", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in the past twelve months, how many disciplinary cases were concluded against civil servants in (a) her Department and (b) its agencies broken down by (i) outcome and (ii) whether the primary allegation related", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860129, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total cost was of (a) settlement agreements and (b) special severance payments made to departing staff in her Department in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860128, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of staff in her Department in each grade were rated in the top performance category in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860127, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of staff in her Department were promoted (a) in-grade and (b) to a higher grade in the last year broken down by (i) performance marking in the previous year and (ii) grade.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860125, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average number of working days lost to sickness absence per full-time equivalent member of staff was in (a) the Department and (b) its executive agencies in the last year; and how many formal performan", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860109, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many environmental assessments relating to HS2 have been carried out since 4 July 2024; in which months those assessments took place; and what the cost was of each assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860094, "askingMemberId": 4788, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to conduct a review of JCVI eligibility criteria and to reinstate free Covid-19 vaccinations for all clinically vulnerable people, in line with the existing appr", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860093, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96798", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the impact of the Revenue Certainty Mechanism on the cost of Sustainable Aviation Fuel compared with conventional jet fuel.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860090, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96797", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the effect of business rates increases at Gatwick, Manchester and other UK airports on passenger ticket prices and airline route planning.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860089, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96796", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the number of passengers who will pay more than \u00a31,000 in Air Passenger Duty on a long-haul Premium Economy family flight by 2027.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860086, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to amend electoral law to prevent British councillors standing for election in overseas countries.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860085, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96794", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the written statement on 19 November 2025, HCWS1071, on Local Government Reorganisation, what is the timetable for the statutory consultation on other two-tier areas ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860084, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96793", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2025, to Question 76604, on Water Charges: Social Tariffs, whether individual households can opt-out of water companies\u2019 charging trials, or otherw", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860083, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, Pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2025, to Question 76604, on Water Charges: Social Tariffs, what is the estimated cost to other customers, (a) in aggregate and (b) cross-subsidy pe", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860082, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to Q260 of the oral evidence given by her Department's Permanent Secretary to the Foreign Affairs Committee on 3 November 2025, HC385, if he will publish Lord ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860080, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96790", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the letter from the Permanent Secretary to the hon. Member for Thirsk & Malton, dated 24 November 2025, on what dates Tim Allan met Tom Baldwin since Mr Allan's appointment, and whether Governm", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860078, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96789", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2025, to Question 88674 on Admiralty House: Council tax and the Answer of 20 November 2025 to Question 88718 on Deputy Prime Minister: Admiralty House, on what specific date", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860077, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96788", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2025 to Question 90311 on Prime Minister: Conflict of Interests, whether the Prime Minister has recused himself from policies on football following advice from the Independe", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860075, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96787", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, further to Cabinet Office Publication of Special Adviser Interests 2024-2025, published on 17 July 2025, what matters Varun Chandra is recused from.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860074, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96786", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 4 November 2025, to Question 85501, on 11 Downing Street: Flats, to the answer of 21 October 2025, to Question 73315, on Deputy Prime Minister: Admiralty House, and to the answer of 20 ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860073, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96785", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of business rates increases at airports on i.) passenger ticket prices and ii.) airline route planning.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860072, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96784", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to extend the child Air Passenger Duty exemption to Premium Economy cabins.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860059, "askingMemberId": 4473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96783", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how frequently does the Department review performance data on Access to Work delivery; and will this data be published regularly.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860058, "askingMemberId": 4473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applicants have reported difficulties communicating with Access to Work in each of the last five years; and what feedback mechanisms exist to improve user experience.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860057, "askingMemberId": 4473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96781", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to make Access to Work application and renewal processes more accessible.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860055, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96780", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when was the last trial for the Sea Viper missile.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860054, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96779", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when was the last trial for the CAMM.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860053, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96778", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when was the last trial for the Brimstone missile.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860052, "askingMemberId": 4473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to simplify and speed up renewals and changes in circumstance to prevent loss of Access to Work support.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860051, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96776", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 27 November 2025 on MOD Security Review, HCWS1103, when did his Department formally adopt the Critical National Infrastructure Knowledge Base.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860050, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 27 November 2025 on MOD Security Review, HCWS1103, how many people are working on the Critical National Infrastructure Knowledge Base; and how many additional people hav", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860049, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 27 November 2025 on MOD Security Review, HCWS1103, if he will list the ranks of personnel that will conduct training with a Remote Piloted Aerial System.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860048, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 27 November 2025 on MOD Security Review, HCWS1103, when he plans to assess the results of the Restricted Airspace pilot.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860047, "askingMemberId": 4473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96772", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to prevent people changing jobs from experiencing long gaps in Access to Work support.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860046, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects HMS Dragon to complete its Power Improvement Project upgrade.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860045, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the Royal Navy vessels that have completed the Power Improvement Project upgrade.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860043, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96769", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 27 November 2025 on MOD Security Review, HCWS1103, if he will set out the time for personnel to complete training for a Remote Piloted Aerial System.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860042, "askingMemberId": 4473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96768", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what quality assurance mechanisms are in place to ensure consistent decision-making across Access to Work caseworkers.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860041, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 27 November 2025 on MOD Security Review, HCWS1103, how much his Department has spent on Remote Piloted Aerial Systems since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860037, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96766", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2025 to Question 70650 on Defence, when he expects the Defence Readiness Bill to be drafted.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860028, "askingMemberId": 4735, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96765", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to Written Statement HCWS867, whether the devolution settlement would prevent the Scottish Government from taking any of the same actions in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860024, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96764", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of encouraging more businesses to become certified B corporations.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859996, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-18T00:00:00", "uin": "96763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to improve access to Disability Living Allowance for children with achondroplasia.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859987, "askingMemberId": 4571, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of delayed access to specialist heart valve treatment has on (a) avoidable unscheduled hospitalisations, (b) deaths on waiting lists and (c) othe", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859986, "askingMemberId": 4571, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96761", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England has made an estimate of the number and proportion of women diagnosed with severe symptomatic aortic stenosis who receive timely treatment compared to men.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859984, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96760", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of Russian interference in the internal affairs of Bosnia and Hercegovina.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859981, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96759", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to correspondence from the hon. Member for Arbroath and Broughty Ferry of 24 October 2025, with the transfer to his department accepted on 3 November 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859974, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when the Minister for the Middle East, North Africa, Afghanistan and Pakistan plans to respond to correspondence from the hon. Member for Arbroath and Broughty Ferry of 23rd ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859964, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent progress her Department has made in ensuring British-Egyptian national Alaa Abd El-Fattah's safe travel to the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859958, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96756", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what analysis her Department has carried out of the potential macro-economic effects (on investment, business growth, rental markets, and savings behaviour) of raising dividend, property and savings income tax rates", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859957, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96755", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the average increase in annual tax paid by households earning between \u00a325,000 and \u00a350,000 following the Autumn Budget 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859956, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96754", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the level of taxation as a result of the Autumn Budget 2025 on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859955, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "96753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of animal-free tests such as the AcutoX for phasing out the LD50 test.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859954, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96752", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people will move into higher tax bands due to the freezing of income tax and National Insurance thresholds for three years; and estimate she has made of the revenue raised through these measures.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859952, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "96751", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what estimate she has made of the number of animals involved in LD50 tests by type of animal; and what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of those tests.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859952", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859947, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "96750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps she is taking to accelerate the phasing out of the use of the LD50 test; and if she will set out a timetable for that phasing out.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859945, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96749", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what funding has been allocated to local authorities in England to lead local community energy schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859944, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what proportion of cars used by ambassadors and embassy officials at UK embassies are manufactured by British manufacturers; and if she will provide a breakdown by manufactur", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859943, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what measures are in place to help increase defence supply chain apprenticeships in the North West.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859942, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of trends in the number of online platforms scraping news articles produced by UK newspapers.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859941, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what proportion of cars used by her Department in the UK were manufactured by a British manufacturer; and if she will provide a breakdown by manufacturer.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859940, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96744", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what process her Department plans to use to allocate funding following the end of UK Shared Prosperity Fund in regions and counties without an elected mayor.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859934, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96743", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how long has the HMRC helpline number 0300 200 3822 been out of service.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859931, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to answer Question 84239 tabled on 22 October 2025 by the Hon Member for Kingswinford and South Staffordshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859925, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96741", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff have been employed by the OBR in each year since it was established.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859923, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96740", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the OBR has cost the public purse for each year since it was established.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859910, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the net expenditure of her Department was on projects related to cultural diplomacy in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859906, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 May 2025 to Question 45822 on Environment Agency and Rural Payments Agency: Equality, if she will publish the Freedom of Information Act response with refer", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859901, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96737", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 2 December 2025 to question 95185, what the updated average annual change in the Welsh Government\u2019s capital budget is between 2025-26 and 2029-30; and whether that budget will increase.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859890, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96736", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff are employed by HMRC in national minimum wage enforcement in 2025-26; and how many of these staff are a) based in Scotland and b) cover Scotland in their role responsibilities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859889, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many in-person inspections were carried out by the Health and Safety Executive in Scotland in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859888, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96734", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Health and Safety Executive inspection officials are based in (a) Scotland, (b) England and (c) Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859887, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many in-person inspections were carried out by the Employment Agencies Standards Inspectorate in Scotland in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859886, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what is the total number of Employment Agencies Standards Inspectorate staff; and how many of these staff are a) based in Scotland and b) cover Scotland in their role responsibilities.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859885, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints were received by the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority with reference to farms in Scotland in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859884, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many in-person inspections were carried out by Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority officers on farms in Scotland in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859883, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96729", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what is the total number of Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority staff; and how many of these staff are a) based in Scotland and b) cover Scotland in their role responsibilities.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859882, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, Department how many UK Visas and Immigration seasonal worker visa scheme compliance visits were conducted in a) England, b) Scotland and c) Wales in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859882", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859875, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96727", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the situation in Nagorno-Karabakh since the signing of the Joint Declaration between Armenia and Azerbaijan in Washington DC in Aug", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859875", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859866, "askingMemberId": 4598, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96726", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her\u00a0Department has made of the potential impact of recent changes to the Motability scheme, including the removal of certain vehicle brands, the introduction of VAT on advance payments and Insurance ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859866", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859854, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96725", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact on future VCT fundraising by reducing upfront VCT Income Tax relief from 30% to 20% from April 2026; and when her Department will publish that impact a", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859854", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859853, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96724", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Food Security and Rural Affairs during Environment, Food and Rural Affairs questions on 13 November 2025, Hansard col 291, o", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859853", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859845, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the maximum sentence will be that a judge could impose on a convicted person when tried under the proposed new swift courts within the Crown Court.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859845", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859837, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an estimate of the number of people who will be sentenced to more than three years in prison by new swift courts within the Crown Court in each of the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859837", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859836, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the introduction of new swift courts within the Crown Court on the number of wrongful convictions.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859836", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859800, "askingMemberId": 4523, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96720", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure (a) a sustainable postal service and (b) the employment rights of postal workers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859800", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859798, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96719", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data his Department holds on the number of people who have newly claimed Universal Credit in each of the last five years by (a) health-related reasons for claiming and (b) the searching-for-work co", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859798", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859797, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the answer of 22 October 2025 to UIN 77348, how many additional assessors have been recruited; and in what locations.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859797", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859795, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complex case coaches (a) are currently employed and (b) have been for each month since June 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859795", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859794, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2025 to Question 62284, whether his Department holds further information on the primary medical conditions of the PIP claimants with an active contract for the Motabili", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859794", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859792, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Personal Independence Payment claimants are in a contract with the Motability Scheme to receive a vehicle by primary medical condition.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859792", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859791, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families in receipt of the child benefit of UC are exempt from the household benefit cap because they (a) receive limited capability for work and work-related activity, (b) are in a grace perio", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859791", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859787, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households who flowed off the household benefit cap because of an exempting benefit had the off-flow outcome due to receiving (a) Employment Support Allowance support group, (b) Disability Livi", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859787", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859783, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, of the households who flowed off the household benefit cap in the quarter to May 2025, how many had the off-flow outcome due to the (a) household\u2019s benefit income being reduced to under the cap levels, ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859783", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859779, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96711", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of (a) removing the two-child limit of UC child benefit and (b) adding that benefit to the exemptions for the household benefit cap on the", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859779", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859778, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96710", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what analysis his Department has done on the increase in households that off-flowed from the benefits cap as a result of the increase in unemployment over the past 13 months, in the context of the 9-mon", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859778", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859777, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the average payment per customer for each primary medical condition, as defined in the Access to Work statistics released by the Department for Work and Pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859777", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859776, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96708", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received the following payment per customer under the Access to Work scheme \u2013 a) \u00a30 - \u00a39,999 b) \u00a310,000 - \u00a319,999 c) \u00a320,000 \u2013 \u00a329,999 d) \u00a330,000 \u2013 \u00a339,999 e) \u00a340,000 - \u00a349,999 f) \u00a350,00", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859776", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859774, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individuals are waiting for their Access to Work application to be processed, and how does this compare to each month since June 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859774", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859765, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many a) neurologists with specialist training in Parkinson\u2019s, b) geriatricians with specialist training in Parkinson\u2019s, and c) specialist Parkinson\u2019s nurses are currently practising in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859765", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859762, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she will take to ensure Great British Railways Retail is treated as a market participant operating under the same terms and conditions as independent rail operators; and what discussions she has had ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859762", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859744, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what her planned timeline is for the establishment of Great British Railways following the passage of the Railways Bill; and if her Department will publish an implementation plan setting out milestones for the ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859743, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many compensation claims were submitted for train operating companies for which her Department is the operator of last resort in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859737, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of a news publishers co-operative to levy online platforms who use and commercialise content produced by the news industry to support lo", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859735, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96701", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will provide a list of assets held by the Crown Estate.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859734, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96700", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of of 7 May 2025 to question 48538, what the timetable is for the Crown Estate negotiating a Partnership Agreement with GB Energy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859712, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96699", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2025 to Question 92671 on Congenital Abnormalities, if he will publish the guidance issued by NHS England on submitting consanguinity and pregnancy data to the", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859711, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96698", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2025 to Question 93956 on Driving Tests, what the marginal cost charged to the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency by the Ministry of Defence is for the deployment of defen", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859710, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96697", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the answer of 27 November 2025 to WPQ 92058, whether he has had discussions with manufacturers who also sell products in China on reluctance to engage with the Trade Remedies Authority beca", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859709, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2025 to Question 93219 on Roads: Biodiversity, whether those schemes undertaking biodiversity net gain requirements are on a voluntary basis.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859708, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96695", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to WPQ 93853, whether she has made any representations on behalf of Carlos Correa and others arbitrarily detained in Venezuela, since the Statement at the Human Righ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859707, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2025 to Question 93226 on Level Crossings, for what reason responsibility for assessing and managing level-crossing down-time rests solely with Network Rail rather than bei", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859706, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96693", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance or advice the National Cyber Security Centre has given to Government Departments regarding the maintenance, purchase or leasing of (a) internal combustion engine based vehicles and (b) electric and", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859705, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96692", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to WPQ 93776, if she will provide a hyperlink to that information, as set out as correct practice in paragraph 234 of the Government's Guide To Parliamentary Work.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859704, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96691", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much central government funding was provided to Transport for London in each financial year from 2007\u201308 to 2024\u201325; and what it is expected to be in 2025-6.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859703, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96690", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the number of bus service miles operated in England outside London in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859702, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96689", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the national average waiting time in weeks was for a practical car driving test in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859701, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96688", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent driving examiners recruited by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency were (a) in post and (b) delivering practical car driving tests in November 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859700, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96687", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) Notices to Improve and (b) written instructions her Department issued to train operating companies for which the Department is the operator in relation to (i) service performance and (ii) financial", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859698, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96686", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the factors causing increased numbers of Education, Health and Care Plans to be issued, including in Oldham.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859697, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96685", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has had discussions with Uber on the recognition of local Trade Union branches for its drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859696, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96684", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the letter from the Permanent Secretary to the hon. Member for Thirsk and Malton, dated 24 November 2025, whether the measures allow Tim Allan to potentially benefit from a rise in the value of", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859693, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to establish Cadet units in Oldham; and whether he will make available funding, resources and organisational assistance to facilitate their formation in areas without Cadet units.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859692, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of making mandatory directions to schools in England to ban mobile phones in the classroom.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859691, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96681", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has to conduct an inquiry, investigation or review into foreign interference at elections and with elected members at all levels.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859689, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96680", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has been made of the potential impact of proposed changes to the annual subscription limit of ISA savings for under-65s on the range of building society lending products.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859688, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to expand access to women's health hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859687, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96678", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an estimate of the (a) value of and (b) tax lost from the black economy in (i) England, (ii) Greater Manchester and (iii) Oldham.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859686, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96677", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Government-registered vehicles are declared as being off the road with a Statutory Off Road Notification (SORN).", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859685, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on probation services in (a) Greater Manchester (b) Oldham for each year from 2015 to date.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859684, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate has been made of the volume, proportion and value of food waste in (a) primary schools, (b) secondary schools, (c) colleges and (d) universities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859683, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96674", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans does the Government have to reduce food waste in the public sector.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859680, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of extending free milk eligibility to the end of the academic year in which a child turns five.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859953, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of excluding car parks, roads and other forms of hardstanding from the definition of Previously Developed Land und", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859951, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason a (a) supermarket with a car park and (b) former industrial site where more than 25% of the site is hardstanding is not considered previously developed land under", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859950, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether potential housing development on (i) supermarkets with car parks, (ii) edge of town retail parks, (iii) train station car parks and (iv) former industrial sites where mor", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859949, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether car parks, roads and other hardstanding in urban areas are brownfield land.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859948, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason the Building Safety Levy (England) Regulations 2025 introduced a new definition of Previously Developed land.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859846, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to extend the scope of the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 to include decapod crustaceans; and what the timeline is for any work required prior to the decision.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859846", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859813, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96666", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps are being taken to ensure there are safeguards when facial recognition is being used for children.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859813", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859803, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96665", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with malaria in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859803", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859790, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96664", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he is taking steps to raise awareness of grief awareness week.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859790", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859786, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96663", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to support young disabled people who cannot work.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859786", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859780, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96662", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking with cabinet colleagues to support young disabled people with complex needs into work.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859780", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859771, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96661", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps are being taken to encourage more smaller businesses to take on apprentices.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859771", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859769, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps are being taken to improve the condition of derelict buildings in town centres.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859769", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859767, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the department are taking to mark international day of disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859767", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859766, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps are being taken to raise awareness in schools of the potential impact of vapes on health.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859766", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859699, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96657", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to launch the Contingent Decision route for the Civil Service Partnership Pension scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859694, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what information her Department holds on the proportion of chatbots deployed in the UK that use search-based functionality as part of their responses; and what assessment she has made o", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859972, "askingMemberId": 4108, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96655", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what formal guidance, policies and risk assessments he has issued to research institutions, NHS bodies and private genomics companies on the sharing of genomic data with foreign entities.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859970, "askingMemberId": 4108, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96654", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria he uses to determine whether companies (a) constitute a threat to national security and (b) are placed under investigation under the Procurement Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859969, "askingMemberId": 4108, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether any Chinese companies have been debarred under the Procurement Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859968, "askingMemberId": 4108, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96652", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any Chinese companies are under investigation under the Procurement Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859967, "askingMemberId": 4108, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96651", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Varun Chandra has had (a) meetings, (b) correspondence and (c) formal communications with representatives of former clients of Hakluyt & Company since taking up his role as Special Adviser.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859966, "askingMemberId": 4108, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96650", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether (a) specific recusals and (b) mitigation measures have been applied to Varun Chandra in relation to any Government (i) decisions, (ii) policies, and (iii) meetings that may intersect with (A) Hakluyt & C", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859965, "askingMemberId": 4108, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96649", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Special Advisers\u2019 Code of Conduct, whether Varun Chandra has declared any financial interests.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860116, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96648", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, further to her answer to Q92990 if she can break down the annual expenditure and the total \u00a34.2 billion into capital and revenue.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859959, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96647", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 26 June to Question 61930, how many P85 forms have been submitted in each month from May 2025 to date.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860071, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Oral Statement on 11 November 2025 entitled Pensions, if he will publish the research findings from the Department's 2007 evaluation on the effectiveness of automatic pension forec", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860070, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Oral Statement on 11 November 2025 entitled Pensions, whether the 2007 report on the effectiveness of automatic pension forecast letters is the one referenced in the Parliamentary ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860069, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the 2007 report on the effectiveness of automatic pension forecast letters is the one referenced in the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman's report entitled Women's State Pension age: ou", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859788, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96643", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Section 4.167 of the Autumn Budget 2025, when her Department plans to publish the solution ensuring that pensioners who only receive the state pension will not (a) have to fill out a tax return and", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859788", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859773, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96642", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 4.167 State Pension and Simple Assessment of the Budget 2025, published in November 2025, when her Department began consulting on this policy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859773", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859772, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96641", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she considered including an assessment of the potential impact of paragraph 4.167 State Pension and Simple Assessment of the Budget 2025, published in November 2025, on costs to the public purse within the B", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859772", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859770, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96640", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Section 4.167 (State Pension and Simple Assessment) of the Budget 2025, if she will publish the cost impact of this policy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859770", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859768, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96639", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pensioners receive the full state pension as their only income.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859768", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860018, "askingMemberId": 1548, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96638", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of requiring public service broadcasters to make all regional programming widely available live on their designated internet programme service", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860016, "askingMemberId": 1548, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the availability on designated internet programme services of public service broadcasters\u2019 live regional programming.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860015, "askingMemberId": 1548, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the threat of Russian-backed disinformation campaigns to (a) peace negotiations between Armenia and Azerbaijan, (b) Armenian democracy ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860014, "askingMemberId": 1548, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96635", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of allegations of the use of bromobenzyl cyanide by Georgian authorities against demonstrators.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860013, "askingMemberId": 1548, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96634", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to help support recent progress by Haiti\u2019s transitional presidential council to hold elections.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859922, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96633", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on the basis of what evidence was the estimate of a 20 per cent time saving for judge only trials made, including the following evidence referred to in the Leveson report (i) the quantitative analyses, (ii) the q", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859963, "askingMemberId": 1466, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96632", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the New Zealand model of Integrated Retirement Communities in formulating the Housing Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859962, "askingMemberId": 1466, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96631", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Housing Strategy will include a plan for Integrated Retirement Communities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859961, "askingMemberId": 1466, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will include a Retirement Occupancy Lease in the forthcoming Housing Strategy as a means to facilitate Independent Retirement Communities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859960, "askingMemberId": 1466, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he last met the Associated Retirement Community Operator (ARCO) to discuss the upcoming Housing Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860067, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96628", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been deported from the USA to the UK in each year since 2016.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860066, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support people living with mental health conditions and on benefits into the workplace.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860064, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support neurodivergent individuals in the workplace.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860008, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he has considered the merits of making it mandatory for DBS checks to be (a) single use and (b) job specific.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860007, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she has taken to prevent third-party sales of DVLA practical driving tests.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860005, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of giving local authorities the power to introduce a temporary Blue Badge scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860004, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she has considered the potential merits of widening the eligibility criteria for the Blue Badge scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860003, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she has taken to (a) repair and (b) improve the condition of road networks in (i) England and (ii) Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860001, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to help reduce housefires in social housing in (a) England and (b) Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859999, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support local authorities to repair roads in (a) England and (b) Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859763, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96618", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2025 to Question 94151 on Terrorism: Victims, if she will take steps to ensure those involved in carrying out acts of terrorism are not (a) invited to the inaugura", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859763", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859736, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96617", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will have discussions with her United States counterpart on the impact of US military action against drug cartels off Latin America since September 2025 on trans-Atlan", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859733, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96616", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with devolved Administrations on ensuring best coordination to restrict the spread of Bluetongue in cattle and sheep.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859835, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96615", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate his Department has made of the cost in (a) time and (b) resource to (i) the Army and (ii) his Department of dealing with problems with the Ajax vehicle.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859835", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859834, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, What times scale he has been given for the noise and vibration issues with the Ajax vehicle to be resolved.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859834", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859833, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his estimate is for carrying out the necessary repairs for the fleet of MAN Logistic Support Vehicles; and how long will it be before the whole fleet is back in service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859833", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859832, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96612", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where were the Army's MAN Logistic Support Vehicle built; and what is the age of the vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859832", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860092, "askingMemberId": 394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96611", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when her Department will host the planned roundtable between Post Office and the major banks to discuss the opportunity of expanding in-person banking services at post offices.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860091, "askingMemberId": 394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96610", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with regards new Aurora trains being introduced on the Midland Mainline, what changes to the internal layout of standard class carriages is being proposed compared to Meridian class trains in order to achieve t", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860033, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to help improve the accessibility of pavements for (a) blind and (b) visually impaired people in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860030, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the levels of recruitment and retention in Lincolnshire Police in the past 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860026, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of community diagnostic hubs in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860023, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96606", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with (1) Chrohn's and (2) Colitis in (a) South Holland and the Deepings and (b) Lincolnshire in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860020, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96605", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to reduce rates of cardiovascular disease in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860017, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce levels of food waste in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860027, "askingMemberId": 177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96603", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what further steps she will take to make the cost of business loans more transparent.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860025, "askingMemberId": 177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96602", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has received representations on the cost of lending required by (a) Maxcap business loans, (b) Capify business loans and (c) Funding Circle\u2019s Flexipay product.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860022, "askingMemberId": 177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96601", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the number of of small business finance applications rejected by (a) high street banks and (b) all banks in (i) total and (ii) just for non asset backed lending applications in the most", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860019, "askingMemberId": 177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96600", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she will bring forward plans to make car insurance more affordable in general and particularly for those living in areas of deprivation.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859985, "askingMemberId": 177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what further steps he will take to help small businesses take advantage of the UK's trade deals.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860088, "askingMemberId": 55, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what engagement she has had with organisations representing motorcyclists in preparation for the Integrated National Transport Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1860087, "askingMemberId": 55, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she plans to publish the Integrated National Transport Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1860087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859642, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the answer of 27 November 2025 to Question 93855, if she will break down those (a) nominal and (b) real terms rises by year.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859642", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859628, "askingMemberId": 5344, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to use AI-powered job-matching tools developed by the private sector to run the new digital service behind the new Jobs and Careers Service.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859626, "askingMemberId": 5344, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the cost of ending the existing Find a Job digital service and transitioning to a new in-house replacement digital service for the new Jobs and Careers Service.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859623, "askingMemberId": 5344, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the level of spending required to develop and run in-house the replacement digital service for the new Jobs and Careers Service.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859623", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859620, "askingMemberId": 5344, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the readiness of the replacement digital service for the new Jobs and Careers Service.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859618, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to ensure there are sufficient rail services on alternative routes when planned maintenance works cause the closure of lines.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859615, "askingMemberId": 5341, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help ensure that food labelling accurately reflects animal welfare practices.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859612, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will consider the treatment of LGBTQ+ refugees when assessing enforced returns to countries with newly established regimes, particularly where a change of government has not resulted", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859610, "askingMemberId": 5166, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether her Department has raised the detention of Bita Shafiei on 13 November 2025 with her Iranian counterparts.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859607, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that LGBTQ+ refugees will not be forcibly returned to countries where they are likely to face persecution.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859604, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to address the 18% of people who are dying annually in poverty in Bristol Central, as identified in Marie Curie's Dying in Poverty 2025 report.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859601, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the timeline for the introduction of new earned income disregards for Housing Benefit claimants in supported housing.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859598, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96584", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are expected to be supported by the introduction of new earned income disregards for Housing Benefit claimants in supported housing.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859596, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96583", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason her department\u2019s July 2025 statutory guidance on Relationships and Sex Education notes that schools should not teach as fact that all people have a gender identity; and how schools should follow", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859593, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96582", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Government of the Islamic Republic of Pakistan regarding the imprisonment of former Prime Minister, Imran Khan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859591, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96581", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to July 2025 statutory guidance on Relationships and Sex Education, whether primary schools are required to teach about same-sex families.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859585, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment has she made of the potential impact of Farming in Protected Landscapes funded projects on children; and whether she will bring forward policy proposals to fund these p", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859583, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96579", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will set out the (a) resources and (b) training her Department will make available to support teachers to implement July 2025 statutory guidance on Relationships and Sex Education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859580, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96578", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) what assessment has the Department made of the impact that delays in UK Visas and Immigration processing times are having on the ability of hospitality businesses to recruit seasonal and skilled w", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859577, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96577", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to respond to the correspondence from the hon. Member for Henley and Thame dated 10 October 2025 on the handling of the transitional protection remedy by teachers\u2019 pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859574, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96576", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of (a) the availability of global supply of the feedstocks used for sustainable aviation fuel and (b) the amounts of that feedstock the Government has identified as being needed for", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859571, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96575", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the sufficiency of current driving instruction in equipping new drivers with the knowledge and practical skills required for safe motorway driving, including appropria", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859569, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made in appointing a chair to the National Inquiry into group based child sexual exploitation and abuse.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859566, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96573", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the Chinese authorities concerning the formal arrest of 18 leaders from Zion church in Guangxi Province; and what steps she is taking", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859561, "askingMemberId": 5244, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96572", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that taxpayer-funded support, including grants and tax reliefs, for AI and data centre funding provides benefits to the public.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859560, "askingMemberId": 5244, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96571", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what plans the Government has to help ensure that local communities receive long-term economic benefits from new AI and data centre developments.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859559, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96570", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much central government funding was made available to the London Borough of Hillingdon in 2024-25 to compensate for costs relating to asylum.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859558, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96569", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2025, to Question 86658, on Asylum: Housing, what specific function or role will the Greater London Authority have in relation to asylum housing.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859557, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96568", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to her Department's press release entitled Review of public order and hate crime legislation, published on 15 November 2025, whether (a) anti-Muslim hatred and (b) the Government's proposed de", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859556, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96567", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2025, to Question 86658, on Asylum: Housing, if she will outline what specific responsibilities and powers will strategic authorities have in this regard; whether", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859555, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96566", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2025, to Question 86342, whether there is an internal document that sets out her Department's new accommodation strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859554, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96565", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish a copy of the current version of the Home Office guidance entitled Hotel Contingency Asylum Accommodation: Local authority version.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859553, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96564", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 5 November 2025, to Question 86340, on Asylum: Housing, for what policy reason the monetary value of Grant 7 and Grant 6 payments to individual local authorities is confident", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859552, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96563", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support the freedom to pray silently in public places.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859551, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96562", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 5 November 2025, to Question 86772, on Asylum: Housing, whether the Home Office holds an unpublished guidance or manual on assessing suitability.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859550, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96561", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 5 November 2025, to Question 85954, on Asylum: Housing, whether there is a guidance document that the Department follows when reviewing and considering a local authority obje", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859549, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96560", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 5 November 2025, to Question 86426, on Asylum: Housing, If she will publish a copy of the pre-procurement documentation sent to potential suppliers of asylum accommodation fo", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859548, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 10 November 2025, to Question 86656, on Hate Crime: Internet, who is the National Police Hate Crime Coordinator and in which public body are they based.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859547, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to the oral statement of 18 November 2025, Official Report, Column 614, on China Espionage: Government Security Response, how the proscription-type tool to disrupt proxy organisations will ope", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859546, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 4 November 2025, to Question 85951, on Asylum: Dental Services, which organisation provides the dental care for asylum seekers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859545, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with respect to the Memorandum of Understanding between the Government of the United States of America and the Government of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland reg", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859544, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96555", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what planning permissions has the Home Office obtained, or intends to obtain, in relation to the asylum seeker accommodation being proposed at the Crowborough, East Sussex military site; and what disc", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859543, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 14 November 2025, to Question 86767, on Counter-terrorism: expenditure, what is the methodology by which local authorities are threat-rated for the purposes of Prevent fundin", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859542, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has provided any support to the Sanctuary City and Sanctuary Council movement since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859541, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96552", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 14 November 2025, to Question 86768, on Radicalism: Expenditure, if he will list the individual sums given to each of those local authorities; and what was the methodology us", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859540, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96551", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what will be the composition of Policing and Crime Boards following the abolition of Police and Crime Commissioners; whether they will contain independent members; how will they be politically balance", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859539, "askingMemberId": 5043, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, steps he is taking to support community-owned and co-operative businesses to have a leading role in high-street renewal.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859538, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96549", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the new taxation of electric vehicles on reaching the UK's net zero targets.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859537, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96548", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential distributional impact of the new taxation of electric vehicles on households with lower incomes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859536, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96547", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the administrative costs to HM Revenue and Customs of implementing the new taxation of electric vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859535, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96546", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the new taxation of electric vehicles on consumer uptake of electric vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859534, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to support GP practices in providing specialist in-house coil clinics, in the content of levels of staffing, clinic space, equipment and stock availability; and what step", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859531, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96544", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the number of unregistered money service businesses currently operating in the United Kingdom.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859529, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96543", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of record keeping requirements for foreign exchange and money remittance transactions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859527, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96542", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to strengthen enforcement action against money service businesses that breach anti money laundering regulations.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859526, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96541", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the level of financial crime linked to non compliant money service businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859525, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96540", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many compliance inspections of money service businesses have been carried out by HM Revenue and Customs in the last twelve months.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859524, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96539", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of anti money laundering controls in bureaux de change and money service businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859523, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96538", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, to what extent young people with long-term health conditions such as epilepsy have been included in the Department\u2019s co-creation process for the forthcoming Schools White Paper.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859521, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the role of Individual Healthcare Plans in supporting the safety and inclusion of pupils with long-term health conditions, such as epilepsy, at school.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859512, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96536", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish a list of businesses that have committed furlough fraud but have not yet repaid the money.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859511, "askingMemberId": 5342, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take legislative steps to expand access rights for swimming and non-motorised craft on inland waters.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859510, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96534", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish a list of businesses that have been required to repay fraudulently claimed furlough money.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859509, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96533", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs expects to recover from outstanding furlough fraud investigations.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859507, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96532", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been recovered by HM Revenue and Customs from furlough fraud to date.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859506, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96531", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, of the firms reported to HM Revenue and Customs for furlough fraud, how many (a) have been investigated and (b) remain to be investigated.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859505, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96530", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of revenue lost to furlough fraud committed during the pandemic.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859504, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96529", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the future annual revenues from pay per mile vehicle tax schemes over the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859503, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96528", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of tax revenues from the new tax on electric vehicles announced in the Autumn Budget 2025 over the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859502, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether there has been a Government response to the 'Common charger for electrical devices: call for evidence', launched on 9 October 2024; and what his policy is on chargers for electrical devices.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859501, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96526", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish all correspondence between herself and the Chair of the Office for Budget Responsibility between 1 October and 1 December.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859500, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96525", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has (a) made an assessment of the current classification of deaf sport within UK sporting-funding frameworks, (b) what consideration her Department has given to the disparity in fundi", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859499, "askingMemberId": 5403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96524", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions she had with the former Chair of the Office for Budget Responsibility on his giving evidence to the Treasury Select Committee following the Budget before his resignation; and if she will publish all", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859493, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96523", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of socioeconomic inequality on (a) stillbirth and (b) neonatal mortality rates; and what cross-government action is being taken to address this.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859492, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce disparities in maternal mortality rates between women from different ethnic backgrounds.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859491, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the removal of ring-fenced funding for maternity services at Integrated Care Board level, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that maternity safety improvements are main", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859490, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason the value of the Local Growth Fund for Wales was reduced from \u00a3633million to \u00a3547million.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859487, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to increase the speed of (a) award decisions and (b) reimbursement payments for the Access to Work scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859486, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859485, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96517", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859484, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96516", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859483, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96515", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859482, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96514", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859481, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859480, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96512", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859479, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96511", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859478, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96510", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859477, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96509", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859476, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859475, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96507", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859474, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859473, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859472, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96504", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859471, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96503", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to address gaps in Post-16 education and skills training provision in Bristol North East.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859470, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859469, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859468, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96500", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859467, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96499", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for the total spend on (i) LinkedIn membership fees (ii) other subscriptions by his Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859466, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96498", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to encourage businesses in Bristol North East to partner with education providers to deliver vocational training and Post-16 skills programmes to local young people.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859465, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2025 to Question 89642 on High Speed 2 Line, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the deferral of works on the Handsacre link on (a) journey times from t", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859464, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96496", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, for the total spend on (a) LinkedIn membership fees and (b) other subscriptions by her Department in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859463, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96495", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the availability of apprenticeship opportunities for young people in Bristol North East constituency; and what plans he has to work with local employers to ex", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859462, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what service standards on timeliness are in place for making decisions on Work Capability Assessments; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce these waiting times.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859461, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of staff undertaking additional work in private hospitals on NHS workforce capacity.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859460, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96492", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reduce delays in the home buying and selling process.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859459, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce delays in County Court proceedings relating to possession or enforcement actions against individuals living in vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859458, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the answer of 20 November 2025 to WPQ 91458, how much revenue local authorities made from (a) traffic junction enforcement, (b) clean air zones and (c) congestion charging in 2024-25.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859454, "askingMemberId": 5038, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department holds data on the distribution of young people of A-level-studying age across different neighbourhoods in Knowsley.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859451, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2025 to Question 90814, what are the names of the third party organisations or agents, acting on behalf of Oxfordshire County Council, that have been provided with vehicle ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859437, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96487", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to WPQ 93460, which roads are covered by the four departures from standards that were granted; and when those decisions were made.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859433, "askingMemberId": 5144, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96486", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to ensure that planning policy does not inhibit the creation of transitional self-contained stepping stone homes for young people who are ready to live i", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859431, "askingMemberId": 5144, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96485", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support local authorities in scaling up the provision of stepping stone homes for young people at risk of homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859423, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96484", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer to WPQ 94294, what is the (a) number (b) proportion of fares per week that will not be the same price or cheaper than the former super off-peak fare on the routes covered.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859420, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96483", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2025 to Question 93455, whether it ceased to be her department's policy that 50% of journeys in towns and cities should be walked or cycled by 2030 when the second Cycling ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859419, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96482", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what is the projected total cost of a third runway at Heathrow, including the consultation process; and who will be responsible for funding the planning and construction.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859418, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96481", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has she made of the potential impact on airline ticket prices from Heathrow Airport of the need to fund the public consultation process for the proposed third runway.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859416, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96480", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, from which local authorities in Cambridgeshire he has received formal submissions for the proposed local government reorganisation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859413, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96479", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of local authorities which may need to issue Section 114s if required to recognise historic DSG deficits on their balance sheets, identifi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859412, "askingMemberId": 5166, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96478", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the impact of moving disabled military veterans from Employment and Support Allowance to Universal Credit on their eligibility for local council tax support schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859411, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96477", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has she made of the potential impact of the estimated \u00a36 billion cost of SEND provision identified by the Office for Budget Responsibility\u2019s Economic Financial Outlook (page 17).", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859409, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96476", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment has he made of the potential impact of the removal of the statutory override on local authority budgets by the end of the 2027-28 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859407, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96475", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much does she estimate the total cost of assuming the full cost of SEND within Central Government will be.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859405, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96474", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of people who were employed in the automotive manufacturing sector in each month since July 2024 up to and including the most recent month for which figures ar", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859403, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Department for Business and Trade on resourcing UK participation in Indo-Pacific market-access programmes.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859402, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) number and (b) proportion of rail journeys were made using (i) advance purchase, (ii) off-peak and (iii) anytime tickets in in each month since and including July 2024 up to and including the most rece", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859400, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what mechanisms she uses to evaluate the performance of UK posts in delivering Indo-Pacific strategic priorities.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859399, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96470", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that UK Indo-Pacific policy is aligned with domestic trade and investment objectives.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859398, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the staffing requirements needed to support expanded UK engagement in Indo-Pacific economic initiatives.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859397, "askingMemberId": 5321, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help improve the ability of police forces to (a) investigate sexual offences, (b) fill gaps in data on violence against women and girls and (c) implement recomme", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859395, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96467", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in respect of train operating companies for which the Department is the operator, how many services were (a) cancelled and (b) delayed by (i) 30 minutes or more and (ii) 60 minutes or more in each month since J", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859394, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96466", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the national HIV surveillance system remains compatible with international reporting standards.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859393, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96465", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to review guidance for local authorities on HIV support service commissioning.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859392, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96464", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new publicly available electric vehicle charge points were (a) installed and (b) brought into operation in each month since July 2024 up to and including the most recent month for which figures are ava", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859391, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96463", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the laboratory capacity required to meet anticipated levels of HIV screening during the HIV Action Plan for England 2025\u20132030 period.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859388, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96462", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his department has made of the potential impact of unionisation within the renewables industry on energy bills.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859385, "askingMemberId": 5321, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96461", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to address cases where DWP staff meet the annual Skilled Worker Visa salary threshold but are affected by the method used to calculate hourly pay.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859384, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96460", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that clinical commissioning structures are prepared for changes arising from the HIV Action Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859383, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96459", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which driving test centres were at 24 weeks wait times in i.) July 2024 ii.) July 2025 and iii.) the latest month for which figures are available.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859381, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96458", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 27 November 2025 to question 93243 on Defence: Procurement, for what reason was Project Magenta cancelled.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859378, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96457", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date was the Gazelle AH Mk1 helicopter withdrawn from service In Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859376, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96456", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of call-handling capacity at MyCSP and what action is being taken to reduce waiting times for members seeking assistance.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859375, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96455", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent steps she has taken to coordinate with a) the co-signatories of the Joint Statement Condemning Atrocities and Violations of International Humanitarian law in Suda", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859374, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96454", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of weather conditions projected over the next three months in Sudan on a) atrocity risks and b) humanitarian access in th", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859373, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96453", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she has taken to engage with a) members of the Sudan Quad and b) other states on coordinated action to i) prevent atrocities, ii) facilitate aid access and iii) su", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859367, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96452", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has plans to review the legislation governing Class F council tax exemptions, specifically the treatment of inherited properties that were occupied at the ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859366, "askingMemberId": 5253, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96451", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to address the 15% of people who are dying in poverty in Mid Fife and Glenrothes every year.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859365, "askingMemberId": 5253, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96450", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to address the 25.9% of working age people who are dying in poverty in Fife every year.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859364, "askingMemberId": 5253, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96449", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of financial insecurity of people at the end of life.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859347, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of plans to reform the immigration settlement system on the number of anaesthetists working in the health service.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859346, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average annual study budget available for resident doctors in England who are undertaking training or professional development is.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859345, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government holds data on the average resident doctor study budget in England compared with that available in (a) Scotland and (b) Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859344, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96445", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has plans to review documentation made public following the expiry of the 20-year confidentiality period relating to gurkha pensions and their alignment to British military standards.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859342, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to implement increased defence expenditure to improve the preparedness and readiness of the armed forces.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859341, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what her Department\u2019s policy objectives are in relation to the UK\u2019s support for Ukraine over the next 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859340, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the current regulatory framework for per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances in (a) food and (b) drinking water.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859339, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will provide a breakdown of the costs incurred by her Department, from 4 July 2024 to date, in the establishment of the Independent Football Regulator.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859335, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96440", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 27 November to question 92601 on Tourism: Taxation, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of Visitor Levies in other jurisdictions on the hospitality sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859333, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96439", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make it her policy to hypothecate revenue raised from a Visitor Levy in London to support the visitor economy in London.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859332, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96438", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make it her policy to split revenue raised from a Visitor Levy in London between the Mayor of London and London boroughs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859328, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96437", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what impact miles driven abroad will have on the calculation of the amount of Electric Vehicle Excise Duty payable per vehicle.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859327, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nurses have specialist training in treating Parkinson\u2019s and working with Parkinson's patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859326, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many geriatricians have specialist training in treating Parkinson\u2019s and working with Parkinson's patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859325, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many neurologists have specialist training in treating Parkinson\u2019s and working with Parkinson's patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859320, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of DCVax-L following its trial at King\u2019s College Hospital.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859316, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96432", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, for what reason the consultation on changes to Feed in Tariffs offers two ways of calculating payments for the generation of solar power at home and selling spare electricity back to the grid", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859314, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96431", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support 18-25 year olds in Devon accessing apprenticeships.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859312, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether her Department provides trauma informed training to their Embassies and Consulates.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859311, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96429", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is planning to take to ensure Parliamentary oversight of the digital ID scheme in relation to the UN Agenda 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859310, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96428", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the press release entitled New digital ID scheme to be rolled out across UK, published on 26 September 2025, what steps he is planning to take to ensure that the scheme cannot be (a) misused, (", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859307, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's get contribution based Employment Support Allowance and are allocated to the Support Group.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859306, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take steps to reduce the rate of pub closures.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859304, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to enhance the UK's diplomatic presence and influence in emerging economies.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859303, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96424", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when will the mandatory digital ID scheme be introduced.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859302, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of climate-related disasters on UK development priorities.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859301, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions the Department has had with international partners on securing global energy supply stability.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859300, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps the Department is taking to support British nationals overseas who are subject to arbitrary detention.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859299, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of UK humanitarian support in conflict-affected regions over the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859298, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to improve cooperation with European partners on countering organised crime and illicit finance.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859297, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96418", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what progress she has made in supporting international efforts to deter hostile state activity.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859296, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96417", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve the timeliness and adequacy of information shared between her Department and local police forces.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859295, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96416", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to improve oversight of biometric data storage and retention across law enforcement agencies.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859294, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96415", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions the Department has had with the police on improving protection for retail workers experiencing abuse or violence.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859293, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96414", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the impact of the recent visa reforms on workforce shortages in key sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859292, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96413", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help support police forces to tackle rising levels of online fraud and scams.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859291, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96412", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to disrupt organised criminal gangs involved in human trafficking.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859290, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96411", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to increase support for victims of domestic abuse, including early intervention and safeguarding.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859289, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96410", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to improve border security technology at ports of entry.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859288, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96409", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of measures to deter small boat crossings in the English Channel.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859287, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with constabularies on reducing response times for burglary and neighbourhood crime.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859286, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has been made of the level of police recruitment and retention rates; and what steps she is taking to help constabularies maintain the number of frontline police officer", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859285, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of trust-level reporting on the use of temporary escalation spaces.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859284, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96405", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to Answer of 1 December 2025 to Question 84488 on Health Services: Buildings, when NHS England expects to publish data on the prevalence of corridor care across trusts.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859283, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96404", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to expand Basildon Hospital\u2019s Accident and Emergency capacity to meet (a) current and (b) projected demand.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859282, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the capacity of Basildon Hospital\u2019s Accident and Emergency department to manage current attendance levels safely.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859281, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96402", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in Accident and Emergency attendances at Basildon Hospital relative to the growth of local population.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859280, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the number of people in the Basildon Hospital catchment area served by its Accident and Emergency department.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859279, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96400", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to publish detailed data on reoffending outcomes by (a) sentence type, (b) offence type, and (c) offender characteristics.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859278, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review the effectiveness of custodial sentences of under 12 months in reducing levels of reoffending.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859277, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the reoffending outcomes for adults released from short custodial sentences; and what steps he is taking to improve those outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859276, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the proportion of offenders who commit a further offence within the one-year follow-up period used in reoffending statistics.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859275, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the current level of conviction and sentencing patterns for immigration offences on immigration enforcement policy.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859274, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase the level of prosecutions for immigration-related offences.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859273, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of reoffending rates of people convicted of immigration offences and sentenced to short custodial terms.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859272, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96393", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data he holds on the rate of reoffending of people convicted of immigration-related offences.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859271, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96392", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risk of reoffending of individuals convicted of immigration-related offences.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859270, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the potential impact of sentencing on deterring illegal entry into the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859269, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of offences created by the Nationality and Borders Act 2022 on illegal entry and arrival.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859268, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of sentencing levels for immigration-related offences under the Nationality and Borders Act 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859259, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to enable working parents to access healthcare without adversely impacting (a) work and (b) childcare commitments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859258, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of managing and attending healthcare appointments on children's school attendance.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859256, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure NHS Online is accessible to people with limited a) digital skills and b) internet access.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859254, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve a) awareness of and b) access to online health care services among families and carers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859253, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that online healthcare provision reflects the needs of diverse modern families.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859250, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason the DVLA continues to rely on postal correspondence for medical driving licence assessments; and whether there are plans to modernise communication methods to allow applicants to communicate wit", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859249, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many medical driving licence applications are currently outstanding for more than (a) 3 months, (b) 6 months and (c) 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859247, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96381", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions she has had with the Department for Transport on improving the quality and quantity of trains on the line between Aberystwyth and Birmingham via Telford.", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859244, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96380", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average waiting time has been for the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency to process medical driving licence applications in each of the past three years; and what steps are being taken to reduce delay", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859242, "askingMemberId": 5058, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to require the creation of additional flood plains in all new developments.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859241, "askingMemberId": 5058, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96378", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to provide additional powers to local authorities to reject planning applications that do not make adequate provision for flooding.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859205, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96377", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of duty-free sales arrangements under the Windsor Framework on Northern Ireland\u2019s airports; and whether she has had discussions with the Northern Irela", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859202, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress her Department has made on the national statutory inquiry into grooming gangs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859195, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to expand BRCA testing to men, including those with male relatives of confirmed BRCA carriers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859194, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will provide guidance, resources, and risk assessment tools to general practitioners to support discussions with patients eligible for targeted prostate cancer screening.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859193, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will publish all submissions made to the Nuclear Regulatory Taskforce.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859191, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of making it a statutory requirement for police officers to record how many suicides they attend.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859190, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96371", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many linear accelerator machines are over (a) 10, (b) 15 and (c) 25 years old by integrated care system.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859188, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96370", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many operations scheduled to be carried out by independent healthcare providers were cancelled by ICBs between April 2024 and 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859187, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many ICBs have had to pause NHS services provided by independent healthcare providers during 2024-25.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859185, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has with ICBs on ensuring delivery of patient care via independent healthcare providers throughout the financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859184, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of survival rates for bladder cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859183, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase research funding for bladder cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859182, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of undertaking a National Bladder Cancer Audit.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859181, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase survival rates for bladder cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859179, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96363", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to expand the use of community optometry services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859178, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to create capacity in hospital eye services by expanding the use of optometry-led diagnostic and treatment pathways.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859177, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of steps taken by Integrated Care Boards to help tackle regional inequalities in access to eye care services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859175, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96360", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that people experiencing financial difficulty are aware of and able to access appropriate (a) financial support and (b) advice during winter months.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859174, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people using the Access to Work scheme in (a) Surrey Heath constituency and (b) Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859171, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2025 to Question 93240 on Armoured Fighting Vehicles: Procurement, what was the a) start and b) finish date of Project RARDEN.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859170, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to announce her funding plan for financing SEND provision.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859169, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the reservoir from which the proposed new town at Tempsford plans to draw its water supply.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859168, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96355", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the reservoir from which the proposed Universal Studios Bedford theme park plans to draw its water supply.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859167, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel are undergoing treatment for hearing loss following operating within an Ajax or Ajax-platform vehicle.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859166, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96353", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what progress has she made in fulfilling the UK contribution to the Child Nutrition Fund in 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859165, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96352", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Prime Minister\u2019s comment that You will see 3,000 neighbourhood police officers on your streets by March in his speech on 1st December 2025, what recent progress has she made in d", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859164, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has he made of the impact of the analysis that the July and November five day resident doctors\u2019 strikes are estimated to have cost \u00a3500 million by the Office for Budget Responsibili", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859163, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96350", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what does he estimate the total cost of implementing digital ID cards to be across the a) resource departmental expenditure limit and b) capital departmental expenditure limit budgets.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859161, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-15T00:00:00", "uin": "96349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pension scheme members affected by the absence of pre-1997 indexation will receive indexation; and how many affected members will not receive indexation because they are in schemes that remain ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859160, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of occupational pension schemes whose pre-1997 pension rights remain unindexed on retired members of those schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859159, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of members of ongoing occupational pension schemes who will not receive pre-1997 indexation.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859158, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to extend pre-1997 pension indexation changes for members of the Pension Protection Fund and Financial Assistance Scheme to members of ongoing occupational pension schemes whose pre-199", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859157, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "96345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to publish a consultation on the VAT treatment of Motability scheme vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859143, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he department has to support wards receiving funding through the Pride in Place programme in a) Telford, b) West Midlands and c) England.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859142, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the cyber-attack on the Legal Aid Agency\u2019s digital systems on the finances of legal aid firms; how many providers have received (a) partial and (b) emergency", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859141, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96342", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many pubs in England have closed in each month since 4 July 2024, broken down by (a) tied pubs, (b) managed houses and (c) freehold or free-of-tie pubs.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859140, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of trends in the level of regional airlines and air links in the last five years on regional communities; and what steps she is taking to support the retenti", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859139, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of air traffic controller recruitment and training capacity; and what steps she is taking to ensure adequate air traffic controller staffing for regional airports.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859138, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of additional dedicated cross-Pennine rail freight capacity to support ports (a) in the Humber Estuary and (b) on the east coast of England, inclu", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859134, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reviewing the adequacy of support available to pensioners in schemes with differing indexation arrangements.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859133, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96337", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether telephone bookmakers will be subject to the increase to Remote Gaming Duty to 40% from 1 April 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859132, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact on road safety in the UK of her Department\u2019s policy allowing people who obtained their driving license abroad to drive in the UK for 12 months without obtain", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859129, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2025 to Question 82809 on Water Companies: Risk Assessment, what steps she is taking to help ensure compliance by local authorities with statutory ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859120, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many deaths have been recorded in inpatient mental health settings in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859107, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to ensure Mental Health Support Teams in schools are trained in Speech and Language therapy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859105, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of safeguards in the online application process for the Breathing Space debt respite scheme in preventing fraudulent or duplicate applications by the sa", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859104, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a mechanism for creditors to seek redress where a Breathing Space certification has been incorrectly granted and financial loss ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859103, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department has collected data on the number of Breathing Space certifications which are subsequently cancelled due to ineligibility.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859102, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department provides to county courts on (a) the verification of documents submitted in support of Mental Health Breathing Space applications and (b) instances in which concerns have been raised ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859101, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he plans to take to help ensure that county courts update their records to reflect the cancellation of Breathing Space certifications.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859100, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that NHS staff are not able to falsely certify documents later used in applications for a Mental Health Breathing Space.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859099, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides to police forces in England regarding the handling of cases where there has been an alleged abuse or fraudulent use of the Breathing Space scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859098, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department took to communicate information regarding recent operational changes to the driving test booking system to Approved Driving Instructors ahead of those changes coming into force.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859097, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96324", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of preventing third parties from booking driving test slots on the range and quality of services driving instructors are able to offer pupils.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859096, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96323", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the answer of 24 November to question 92054 on Independent Football Regulator: Political Parties, if she will publish the data on the additional political donations made by David Koga", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859095, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the Problem Gambling Severity Index score for players of (a) The National Lottery, (b) Society Lotteries, and (c) instant win scratch cards.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859094, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to Minister's statement to the House on 26 June 2025, what assessment she has made of the merits of comparing identical time frames.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859093, "askingMemberId": 4828, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the effectiveness of the monitoring of early foetal development in patients by trusts and (b) trends in the level of variations in that monitoring by ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859092, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to combat antisemitism (a) in secondary schools, (b) in colleges, and (c) on university campuses.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859091, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96318", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to cease the purchasing of non-essential items, including vapes, for illegal migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859090, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96317", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, (a) if there will be exemptions made to her ticket price cap policy and (b) what criteria is used to judge this.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859089, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96316", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans make an assessment of the use of (a) fibrous forms of talc, (b) tremolite and (c) actinolite in products used by the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859088, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish a timeline for allocating expenditure of the \u00a3400 million capital funding for grassroots sporting facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859087, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the use of (a) gyms, (b) swimming pools, and (c) leisure centres alongside weight-loss drugs.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859086, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions regarding the inclusion of physical activity and exercise-based solutions within programmes aimed at reducing ill he", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859085, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to help ensure that (a) gyms, (b) swimming pools, and (c) leisure centres are used to help reduce (i) health and (ii) socioeconomic inequalities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859084, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96311", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of business or employment tax rises on (a) gyms, (b) swimming pools, and (c) leisure centres.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859082, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96310", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, of recent illegal working arrests, how many have been removed from the United Kingdom.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859081, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of foreign nationals claiming welfare benefits.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859080, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that the State Pension Benefit will be available under the current conditions to those entering the workforce in the financial year 2025-2026.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859079, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96307", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the emigration of (a) 18-25, (b) 26-35, (c) 36-49, and (d) 50+ years old on (i) the levels of revenue raised through taxation and (ii) the sustainability of th", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859644, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96306", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Blaenau Gwent and Rhymney, representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of drinking water provision in Tothill Street.", "answeringBodyId": 18, "answeringBodyName": "House of Commons Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859644", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859643, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96305", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Blaenau Gwent and Rhymney, representing the House of Commons Commission, by which date all lifts in Tothill Street will be fully operational.", "answeringBodyId": 18, "answeringBodyName": "House of Commons Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859643", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859637, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the letter from the Minister of State for Rail to the hon. Member for St Albans of 28 November 2025, reference MC/00054165 whether she has received representations from Govia Thameslink Railwa", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859637", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859634, "askingMemberId": 4786, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to Question 92229, whether his Department paid for British armed forces personnel to attend courses in Israel since October 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859634", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859631, "askingMemberId": 4786, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to Question 92229, which courses British armed forces personnel have attended in Israel since October 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859631", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859588, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the National Insurance contribution holiday for the employers of veterans will be in place for each remaining financial year of the current Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859564, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will set out what steps were taken in the Autumn Budget 2025 in respect of the Listed Places of Worship Grant Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859533, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Royal Navy trial high-tech autonomous mine hunting capability, published on 10 December 2024, how many trials have taken place as part of the Apollo Marit", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859532, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has held discussions with service chiefs regarding the spending envelope for the Defence Investment Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859530, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) UK-based SMEs and (b) mid-tier suppliers have been offered support through the Defence Supplier Capability Development Programme since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859528, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement by the Minister for the Armed Forces on 27 November on MOD Security Review, HCWS 1103, how many contracts have been placed for Remote Piloted Aerial Systems since 5 July 20", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859522, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the official closing date under section 14 of the Inquiries Act 2005 was for the public inquiries entitled (a) Robert Hamill Inquiry and (b) Billy Wright Inquiry.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859520, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the official closing date under section 14 of the Inquiries Act 2005 was for the public inquiry entitled ICL Inquiry.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859519, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the official closing date under section 14 of the Inquiries Act 2005 was for the public inquiry entitled Al-Sweady Inquiry.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859518, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the official closing date under section 14 of the Inquiries Act 2005 was for the public inquiries entitled (a) Inquiry into the circumstances of the Death of Bernard Lodge at Manchester Prison on 28 August 1", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859517, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the official closing date under section 14 of the Inquiries Act 2005 was for the public inquiry entitled Mid Staffordshire NHS Foundation Trust Inquiry.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859516, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the official closing date under section 14 of the Inquiries Act 2005 was for the public inquiries entitled (a) Anthony Grainger Inquiry, (b) The Litvinenko Inquiry and (c) Independent Inquiry int", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859515, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the official set up date under section 5 of the Inquiries Act 2005 was for the public inquiry entitled Inquiry into the circumstances of the Death of Bernard Lodge at Manchester Prison on 28 August 1998.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859514, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96288", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the official set up date under section 5 of the Inquiries Act 2005 was for the public inquiry entitled Mid Staffordshire NHS Foundation Trust Inquiry.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859513, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96287", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the official set up date under section 5 of the Inquiries Act 2005 was for the public inquiries entitled (a) Jermaine Baker, (b) Manchester Arena Inquiry and (c) Anthony Grainger Inquiry.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859508, "askingMemberId": 4803, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of people being held in Accident and Emergency departments due to unavailability of local NHS mental health beds on patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859498, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many specialist nurses in Parkinson's there are.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859497, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many geriatricians with specialist training in Parkinson's there are.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859495, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many neurologists with special training in Parkinson's are there.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859494, "askingMemberId": 4803, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Social and Affordable Homes Programme plan to build 300,000 homes over ten years, of which 180,000 will be for social rent, do these targets exclude (a) com", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859488, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the Structures Fund will be allocated towards the funding of the Lower Thames Crossing.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859457, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Universal Credit claimants with dependent children are in the light touch or working conditionality groups.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859456, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the number of Universal Credit households with dependent children reporting fewer than (a) 16, (b) 30 and (c) 35 hours of work per week.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859455, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of Universal Credit claimants with dependent children are in (a) full-time or (b) part-time work.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859453, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96277", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for every year since 2017, what proportion of Universal Credit claimants with dependent children are (a) in work and (b) not in work.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859452, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96276", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the average duration of a Universal Credit claim that was started in a) 2021, b) 2022, c) 2023, d) 2024 and e) 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859450, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96275", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the average duration of a Universal Credit claim for someone who begins a claim at age a) 18, b) 19, c) 20, d) 21, e) 22, f) 23 and g) 24.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859449, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, will he provide projections for the number of face-to-face assessments on a national basis for each month of 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859448, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families there were in each region in England and Wales with (a) one child, (b) two children, (c) three children, (d) four children, (e) five children, (f) six to eight children, (g) eight to 1", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859447, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the membership of the Timms Review steering group will be published.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859446, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of Universal Credit starts in each of the last 5 years were (a) new benefit claimants and (b) claimants transitioning from legacy benefits through managed migration.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859445, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96270", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, wow many employees in the United Kingdom take part in a salary sacrifice scheme in the (a) public and (b) private sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859444, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of recent changes to salary sacrifice arrangements on employees\u2019 pension savings.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859443, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the Autumn Budget 2025 on the number of NEET young people.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859442, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many NEET young people (a) live with their parents or guardians and (b) live independently.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859441, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96266", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many NEET young people are parents, broken down by month since January 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859440, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what projections his Department has made of numbers of NEET young people for each quarter until the end of this Parliamentary term.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859439, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of current numbers of NEET young people on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859438, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the Environment and Climate Change Committee's recommendations published in its policy letter to her, dated 28 October 2025, on Waste Crime.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859436, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Integrated Care Boards can continue to provide consistent care and support to service users while restructuring processes are ongoing.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859430, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what volume of rail freight in tonne-kilometres was moved in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859429, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the level of net Government support to the rail sector per passenger journey in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859428, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many used electric vehicles were sold in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859427, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff currently work for DfT Operator Limited.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859426, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96257", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of new cars registered in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024 were zero-emission vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859425, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96256", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of rail journeys used fully digital tickets in (a) November 2025 and (b) each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859414, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of passenger notification procedures for planned engineering works that result in disruption to rail services.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859404, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what measures are in place to ensure that assistance services in rail stations for disabled and vulnerable passengers remain functional during significant service disruptions.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859401, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the current legal protection regime for decapod crustaceans; and what steps is she taking to strengthen protections of the welfare of de", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859396, "askingMemberId": 4658, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to ensure that rail operators provide sufficient staffing and passenger management during major route disruptions.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859389, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96251", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate the Department has made of the level of change in the number of households exempt from the benefit cap following the Autumn Budget 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859387, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96250", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Crime and Policing Bill on the number of young people arrested at protests.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859386, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96249", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Crime and Policing Bill on the right to protest without fear of criminal sanction.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859382, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96248", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether fire services are classified as safety-critical work for the purposes of the HSE's classification of 12-hour shifts as undesirable for such work.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859380, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96247", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made any assessment of the impact on family life of twelve hour shifts within the fire service.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859379, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96246", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what comparative assessment his Department has made of fires attended by fire services affecting i) heritage sites ii) tower blocks and iii) HMOs during a) the night hours and b)", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859377, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the a) fatality and b) injury\u00a0rate of fires attended by fire services during the night hours compared with fires during daytimes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859370, "askingMemberId": 4598, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96244", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to help ensure that telecommunications operators engaging in permitted development applications for 5G infrastructure adequately consult and e", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859363, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96243", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she will consider extending the proposed alignment of the personal allowance for pensioners with the new State Pension rate.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859362, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Royal Navy trial high-tech autonomous mine hunting capability, published on 10 December 2024, how many Apollo Maritime Counter Measure vessels has he orde", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859361, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June to Question 57673 on Military Intelligence, if he has a target date for the full implementation of the Digital Targeting Web.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859360, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June to Question 57673 on Military Intelligence, whether there have been any further industry days on the Digital Targeting Web since 18 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859358, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March to Question 34903 on Defence: Procurement, if he will list the other sectors outside the defence sector who will be consulted on the Defence Small and Medium Enterprise Support ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859357, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March to Question 34903 on Defence: Procurement, how many staff will be employed as part of the Defence Small and Medium Enterprise Support Hub.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859356, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March to Question 34903 on Defence: Procurement, who will staff the Defence Small and Medium Enterprise Support Hub.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859355, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March to Question 34903 on Defence: Procurement, whether any new staff will be recruited as part of the Defence Small and Medium Enterprise Support Hub.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859354, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March to Question 34903 on Defence: Procurement, who will lead the Defence Small and Medium Enterprise Support Hub.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859353, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New robots lead the way in bomb disposal innovation, published on 5 February 2025, how many trials for robot bomb disposal have taken place since 5 Februa", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859352, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Storage facility for over 900 vehicles completed at MOD Ashchurch, published on 5 March 2025, if he has a target date for the demolition of 58 existing bu", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859351, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Storage facility for over 900 vehicles completed at MOD Ashchurch, published on 5 March 2025, when all 13 new buildings will be delivered as part of the V", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859350, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96231", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on the UK Maritime Electronic Warfare Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859349, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many TEKEVER AR3 uncrewed air platforms he has procured since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859348, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Underwater robot could improve pipeline and cable security, published on 9 June 2025, when the last trial on underwater robots took place.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859343, "askingMemberId": 4788, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96228", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken under the Replacing Animals in Science strategy to establish a clear timeline for phasing out all animal experiments.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859338, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the report of the United Nations High Commissioner for Human Rights, entitled Database of all busin", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859337, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the number of Israeli strikes on Lebanon since 27 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859336, "askingMemberId": 4676, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of refusing new oil developments at Rosebank.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859334, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November to Question 92922 on Fly-tipping, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of a single responsible body to receive and investiga", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859331, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a child-focused victim-assistance component of any demining funding for Sudan to support (a) prosth", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859330, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps the UK is taking to help ensure the Rapid Support Forces and Sudanese Armed Forces urgently engage with the United Nations to (a) sign and (b) implement action pla", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859329, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96221", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2025 to Question 84311 on Sudan: Armed Conflict, how the UK is leveraging its membership of the UN working group on Children and Armed Co", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859324, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to protect the welfare of live decapod crustaceans while held in commercial premises prior to sale.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859323, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96219", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what mechanisms exist to support waste-reduction trials with NHS trusts.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859322, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96218", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has had discussions with NHS trusts on the potential reuse of polypropylene ward curtains.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859321, "askingMemberId": 4612, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, which nuclear technologies are being considered by Great British Energy - Nuclear as part of its investigation into Scottish sites for new nuclear development.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859319, "askingMemberId": 4612, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96216", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he expects Great British Energy \u2013 Nuclear to (a) complete its study into potential Scottish sites for new nuclear development and (b) make the findings of that study publicly available.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859318, "askingMemberId": 4612, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96215", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether Great British Energy - Nuclear\u2019s assessment of potential Scottish sites for new nuclear development includes (a) previously used nuclear sites and (b) new sites.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859317, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96214", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce levels of NHS waste.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859309, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96213", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on (a) allocating funding and (b) identifying opportunities for investment by the Defence Growth Deal in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859308, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to review UK National Archive material relating to Britain\u2019s administration of the Mandate in Palestine between 1917 and 1948.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859305, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96211", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many private aircraft landed at Leuchars Station between 28 September 2025 and 6th October 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859267, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96210", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any Ministers have unspent criminal records.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859266, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96209", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the name of each Mission Board is.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859265, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96208", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Direct Ministerial Appointments are in post across government; and how many are paid.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859264, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96207", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the answer of 28 October 2025 to Question HL10808 on Official Residences, for what reason the Defence Secretary was allocated use of Flat 2 of Admiralty House.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859263, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96206", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Information Commissioner decision notice of 29 October 2025, Ref IC-362303-N0J6, para 27, whether Lord Alli was on the list provided.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859262, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96205", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many months each of the Ministerial flats in Admiralty House have been empty for.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859261, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96204", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many additional households will become subject to the Household Benefit Cap following the removal of the two-child limit on the Universal Credit child element.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859260, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96203", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the answer of 28 October 2025 to Question HL10808 on Official Residences, whether his Department paid council tax on the Ministerial residence in Admiralty House between 9 September and 4 Novem", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859257, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96202", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households are exempt from the Household Benefit Cap solely as a result of receiving (a) Personal Independence Payment and (b) Carer\u2019s Allowance by region.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859255, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96201", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households are exempt from the Household Benefit Cap solely as a result of receiving (a) Disability Living Allowance and (b) Attendance Allowance by region.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859251, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96200", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of total benefit income received by the average benefit-capped household is accounted for by (a) Universal Credit excluding child elements, (b) the Universal Credit child element, (c) Ho", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859248, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96199", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to assist landowners in coordinating and accessing relevant grants and schemes for the long-term moorland restoration required following the Fylingd", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859246, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96198", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to establish a financial support scheme for farmers, graziers and landowners impacted by major wildfires, equivalent to the Farming Recovery Fund available for", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859245, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96197", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the economic impact of the Fylingdales Moor fire on businesses that were (a) evacuated and (b) made inaccessible due to road closures; and what fin", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859243, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96196", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing a financial recovery framework for major wildfire incidents, equivalent to the Flood Recovery Framework, to pr", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859236, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96195", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Railways Bill on accessibility at train stations.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859232, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96194", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an estimate of the number and demographic profile of savers impacted by the reduction in the annual cash ISA allowance; and whether she plans to introduce alternative saving and investment incen", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859218, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96193", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that when errors in earnings submissions to HMRC are self-identified and corrected, those corrections are communicated promptly and accurately to the Department for Work", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859216, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96192", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that information received from HMRC regarding earnings is accurate and that any errors are identified and corrected swiftly, so that Universal Credit claima", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859201, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96191", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has issued recent guidance to Departments on the disclosure of political activity at the same time as the announcement of appointments.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859200, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96190", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to page 122 of the OBR, Economic and Fiscal Outlook, November 2025, CP1439, 26 November 2025, if he will itemise the cost of Digital ID Cards in each of those three years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859197, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96189", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Prime Minister plans to recuse himself from the appointments process for non-executive board members of the independent football regulator.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859196, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96188", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Prime Minister will make it his policy to appear before the Liaison Committee before Christmas recess.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859173, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96187", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of officials at each Senior Civil Service grade completed the One Big Thing 2024 Innovation Masterclass from each Department and executive agency; and if he will provide this informa", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859156, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96186", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what actions have been taken in response to recommendations made by the Independent Case Examiner in relation to Child Maintenance Service complaints in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859155, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96185", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Maintenance Service cases in each of the last five years the Independent Case Examiner identified maladministration; and what common failings were identified.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859154, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96184", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints about the Child Maintenance Service were received in each of the last five years, and how many were (a) upheld, (b) partly upheld and (c) not upheld.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859153, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department gives to the Child Maintenance Service to verify income for self-employed parents and those operating via company structures; and what mechanisms are in place to improve acc", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859152, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Department plans to publish a child maintenance arrears reduction strategy for the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859137, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96181", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimates National Highways has made of a) the average daily number of HGV movements to and from Immingham Port, b) expected daily HGV movements over the next five years, and c) whether current road capaci", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859136, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96180", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what comparative estimate his Department has made of (a) electricity prices for energy-intensive industries in (i) the UK and (ii) France and Germany and (b) grid and network charges in the U", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859135, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96179", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the fiscal cost of Benefit-in-Kind rates for zero-emission company cars, including (a) the cost of the 3 per cent rate in 2025\u201326, (b) the revenue forgone when the rate was 0", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859131, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96178", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken for Developed Vetting renewals.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859130, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96177", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 10 October 2025, to Question 70464, on Government Communication Service: Audit, what is the timetable for the completion of the current annual data collection.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859128, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment has been made of the effectiveness of plans to reduce vehicle generated air pollution in Greater Manchester as an alternative to the now cancelled charging Clean Air Zo", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859127, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children were referred to Prevent in each year from 2015 to date by age.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859126, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of funding for canal maintenance.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859125, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what progress he has made on rolling out gas and electric smart meters to properties in England.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859124, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with car manufacturers on reducing the risk of stolen catalytic converters through design and technology.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859123, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether she plans to bring forward proposals to require VPN providers to undertake age verification checks on UK users.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859122, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of financial restrictions on the ability of victims of civil online defamation and harassment to take action.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859121, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to implement remote electronic voting for (a) UK and (b) local elections.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859119, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96168", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) primary and (b) secondary schools without libraries in England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859118, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96167", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of vulnerable users of telecare alarms who have (a) successfully transferred and (b) not yet transferred from analogue to digital systems.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859117, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96166", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of profit per placement for private children\u2019s homes in England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859116, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96165", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the adherence of private children\u2019s homes to notifying the receiving local authority of vulnerable young people being placed in their area.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859115, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of fuel poverty amongst home owning pensioners in (a) England, (b) Greater Manchester and (c) Oldham.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859114, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96163", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of future road and rail freight capacity in the North of England following the cancellation of HS2.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859113, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96162", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of invasive weed removal from publicly owned land in England.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859112, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96161", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with local government on improving community cohesion and building stronger local relationships between people from different backgrounds.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859111, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96160", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of modern slavery adherence by employers who have published Modern Slavery statements.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859110, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96159", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what financial support she has provided to areas affected by HS2 cancellation for inherited liabilities and costs incurred.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859109, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96158", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of train services between Manchester and London in 2025; and how much has been spent on delay repay compensation to customers on those services in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859108, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether she plans to being forward legislation to (a) ban and (b) limit mobile phone and broadband above inflation contract increases.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859083, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Government action to protect children from abusive parents, published on 22 October 2025, how he plans to enact the repeal of the presumption of parental ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859078, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96155", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will hold discussions with the hon. Member for Angus and Perthshire Glens on the work of her Department's Murder and Manslaughter Team.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859231, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96154", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what modelling she has undertaken on applying National Insurance to salary-sacrificed pension contributions above \u00a32,000; and whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of that measure on pension con", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859230, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96153", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of applying National Insurance to salary-sacrificed pension contributions above \u00a32,000 from 2029 on small and medium-sized employers, pension take-up and long-ter", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859229, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that apprenticeship funding announced in the Autumn Budget 2025 reaches high-demand sectors in the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859228, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of apprenticeship measures in the Autumn Budget 2025 on small and medium-sized employers in Aldridge-Brownhills constituency and the Black Count", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859227, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the skills measures in the Autumn Budget 2025 on adult learners in communities in Aldridge-Brownhills constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859226, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of skills funding announced in the Autumn Budget 2025 on the adequacy of engineering, advanced manufacturing, logistics, construction and health and s", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859225, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of electric vehicle charging infrastructure in the West Midlands; and whether she plans to provide additional support for installing public EV chargers across Aldrid", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859224, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of funding for buses in the Autumn Budget 2025 on bus routes serving Aldridge-Brownhills constituency; and whether her Department plans to issue guidance to ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859222, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-09T00:00:00", "uin": "96146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the impact of the Budget\u2019s roads funding announcements on tackling congestion hotspots in Aldridge-Brownhills, including the A452, A461, Chester Road, Walsall Wood Road and Brown", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859221, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that additional capital funding for roads, rail and bus networks announced in the Budget is allocated fairly across the West Midlands, including to areas across Ald", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859215, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish any impact assessments on the potential displacement of visitors away from levy-charging areas of the West Midlands to neighbouring counties without such charg", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859214, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the impact of granting the Mayor of the West Midlands Combined Authority powers to levy a mandatory charge on overnight stays on smaller visitor ec", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859213, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional support, will be provided to West Midlands councils in 2025-26, 2026-27 and 2027-28 to manage growing SEND costs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859212, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he will require the Department for Education or newly responsible central government bodies to publish borough-level data on SEND provision, EHCP timeliness and outcomes once funding is centralised, to ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859211, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government will maintain or reform the \u201csafety valve\u201d and \u201cdeliverability\u201d programmes for local authorities following the centralisation of SEND funding; and how councils such as Walsall will be sup", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859210, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96139", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether local authorities will be required to repay accumulated DSG deficits before 2028-29, or whether such deficits will be written off as part of the transition to central gov", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859209, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the OBR\u2019s conclusion that cumulative local authority SEND deficits may reach \u00a314 billion by 2027-28, and what implications this has for the financi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859208, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact on West Midlands local authorities of the Government\u2019s decision in the Autumn Budget to transfer full responsibility for fundi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859252, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96136", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will consider leading a workforce strategy for the advice sector to support the aims of the Get Britain Working white paper.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859240, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps are being taken to find prisoners who were released by accident.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859239, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of unregistered pharmacies that are operating.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859238, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96133", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information her Department holds on the number of schools that took part in the Youth Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859237, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are being taken to help support the maritime sector.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859235, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of reintroducing a milk strategy for schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859234, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the price of school uniforms.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859233, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to improve road safety outside schools.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859223, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refusals there have been for firearms licenses in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859220, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many confirmed cases of avian flu has there been in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859219, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many confirmed cases of blue tongue there has been in the last 24 months.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859217, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the adequacy of the current palliative care strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859207, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to improve the planning system.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859206, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96123", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to hold housing developers accountable for defects in newly built homes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859204, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the number of families in temporary accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859203, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96121", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to improve housing provision.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859198, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of the number of people with Parkinson's in the Employment and Support Allowance Support Group.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859639, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to bring forward a strategy for dental health research.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859639", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859151, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96118", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2025 to Question 83750 on Health Services: Innovation, what mechanisms are in place to monitor and evaluate the successful adoption and diffusion of health inno", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859150, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96117", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department provides to school trusts to safeguard against cyber attacks and to protect children's personal data.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859148, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment has she made of the implications for UK waste disposal and consumer product policy of the levels of unwanted electrical items discarded annually by households which cou", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859147, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96115", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to align the UK with EU Directives 2024/1781/EU, 2024/1799/EU and 2024/825/EU.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859146, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will take steps with the Office for Product Safety and Standards to ensure that regulations and repairability indexes for small electrical devices promote not only professional repair s", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859144, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology,\twhether Innovate UK will resume its Smart Grants funding stream to support innovation-led start-ups.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859372, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to extend the Fruit and Vegetable Growers Scheme beyond December 31st 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859369, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government plans to publish a detailed roadmap for improving national missile defence capabilities, including timelines and funding commitments.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859368, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96110", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment his Department has made of the UK\u2019s vulnerability to long-range missile threats, including ballistic and cruise missile systems; and what steps he is taking to strengthen integrated air and", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859359, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96109", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether there will be a Spring Statement in 2026 to accompany the OBR's Spring Forecast 2026; and whether the OBR's Spring Forecast 2026 will include the scoring of new measures announced since Autumn Budget 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859359", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859149, "askingMemberId": 3912, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96108", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government intends to provide exceptional funding support to Bedford Borough Council to cover costs incurred as a result of the Cleat Hill explosion on 19 October 202", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859145, "askingMemberId": 3912, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will provide a response to the application submitted by Bedford Borough Council for exceptional funding support to cover costs incurred as a result of the Cleat Hill explos", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859435, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to provide certainty to industry in relation to the expansion of the UK Emissions Trading Scheme to maritime.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859434, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions her Department has had with the Department for Energy Security and Net Zero on prioritising access to the national grid for port electrification to support ports who wish to offer onshore power", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859432, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to support the provision of onshore power supply for ports across the UK, including in Northern Ireland, in relation to onshore power supply for ferries and cruise shi", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859424, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96103", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate she has made of the contribution of fuel duty to inflation and the cost of living; and whether she will review current rates in the context of wider price pressures.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859422, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96102", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the impact of current fuel duty rates on the road freight and logistics sector; and whether her Department plans to bring forward measures to reduce transport costs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859421, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment has been made of the effectiveness of current regulatory protections, such as age verification and advertising restrictions, in preventing gambling among young people.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859417, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the availability and effectiveness of rehabilitation support for individuals with a gambling addiction within the criminal justice system.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859415, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of gambling-related harm among individuals within the criminal justice system; and what steps he is taking to improve screening and support for problem gambling in pr", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859410, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to require gambling operators and online platforms to provide greater transparency regarding how gambling advertisements are targeted and delivered to users.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859408, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96097", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of current regulatory frameworks governing gambling advertising across broadcast, online, and social media platforms.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859406, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the Cameroon authorities concerning the recent kidnapping and detention of Christian clergy in the Northeast region.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859489, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the annual figures for payments made to each of NHS Resolution's panel law firms since the current legal framework came into effect in March 2022; and, in each case, what proport", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859199, "askingMemberId": 1572, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the report into the cost of clinical negligence being prepared by David Lock KC.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859371, "askingMemberId": 1489, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps the Government is taking to safeguard individuals in response to rapid developments in artificial intelligence, including protecting 1) the general public and 2) Members of P", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859562, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions in the past three years has cargo being transported in UK waters been found to contain oil sourced in or through Russia.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859172, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96091", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is her policy to provide full access to veterinary medicines for Northern Ireland via the Veterinary Medicines Internal Market Scheme from 1 January 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859162, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many organisations and companies (a) reported cyber incidents in the last 12 months and (b) had adopted the Cyber Essentials scheme beforehand.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859106, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96089", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, approximately how many people have become tax payers since the \u00a312,570 personal allowance was frozen in 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859390, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what data her Department holds on gender disparities in access to youth sports training facilities; and what steps she is taking to decrease those disparities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859496, "askingMemberId": 373, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "96087", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has assessed the potential implications for open justice of the Solicitors Disciplinary Tribunal\u2019s decision to bar the press and public from recent proceedings.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859192, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the capacity of GP services to meet demand in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859189, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been (a) investigated and (b) prosecuted for attempting to impersonate someone else on a Secure English language test in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859186, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96084", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been (a) investigated and (b) prosecuted for cheating on Secure English language tests in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859180, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support older people experiencing financial hardship in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859176, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of access to NHS dental services for disabled patients in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859645, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96081", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 2 December 2025 to question 95016, whether the hon. Member for (a) Wolverhampton North East, (b) Leeds South West, (c) Bournemouth East, (d) Luton North, (e) Bassetlaw, (f) Blyth and Ashing", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859645", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859315, "askingMemberId": 177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the answer of 1 December 2025 to Question 93633, if he will publish that assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859313, "askingMemberId": 177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "96079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the findings of Independent Commission on Neighbourhoods, whether he will take steps to encourage private sector growth in the most deprived neighbourhoods in E", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859014, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of developing a Modern Service Framework for respiratory health.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Respiratory Diseases: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859015, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether an assessment has been made of the potential impact of changes in parish council precepts on council tax.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parish and Town Councils: Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859013, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure landlords let accommodation is fit for human habitation as set out in the Homes (Fitness for Human Habitation) Act 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Rented Housing: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859012, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will introduce a ringfenced element for (a) furniture and (b) appliances through the Crisis and Resilience Fund.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crisis and Resilience Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859016, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he had had with Kent County Council on best value since May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kent County Council: Best Value", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859008, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "96073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential financial impact of the proposed (a) application of VAT on payments for higher value vehicles and (b) removal of the Insurance Premium Tax exemption for vehi", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859007, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-16T00:00:00", "uin": "96072", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to remove the VAT exemption for vehicles adapted for use by disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859002, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2025 to Question 83204, what step he is taking to secure a recurrent budget for abiraterone in high risk, non-metastatic prostate cancer, in the context of it b", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Abiraterone", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858989, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has assessed how alcohol labelling reforms could support local public-health and community-based initiatives aimed at reducing alcohol-related harm, particularly in areas wit", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alcoholic Drinks: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858988, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has assessed the importance of including accessible behaviour-change and drinking moderation tools, including links to digital health support, as part of the new mandatory al", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alcoholic Drinks: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858980, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he will review the current eligibility criteria for NHS-funded COVID-19 vaccinations, in light of the emergence of a new variant and rising hospitalisations.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858967, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that households do not face further rises in energy bills if the support announced in the recent Budget is not extended beyond the initial three-", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858965, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of whether the energy bill support measures announced in the recent Budget will cease after the stated three-year period.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858959, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of adopting a national exemption for domestic abuse survivors from housing-related debt rules in social housing allocation pol", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Social Rented Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858958, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of local authority housing-related debt rules on domestic abuse survivors who are placed in temporary accommodatio", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Social Rented Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858952, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measures are in place to prevent delays to child maintenance proceedings arising from the non-submission of required documents by a paying parent; and how the Department ensures that such delays do", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858952", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858949, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-11T00:00:00", "uin": "96062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Department is taking to ensure that the Child Maintenance Service has effective mechanisms to prevent high earners from reducing their maintenance liabilities through the diversion of inc", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858929, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96061", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his department has made of the impact of furniture poverty on homelessness prevention and recovery; and if he will explore possibilities to use furnished tenancie", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rented Housing: Furniture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858928, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of children who have experienced homelessness being moved into properties with (a) unsafe or (b) no flo", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rented Housing: Furniture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858927, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96059", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his department's policies of trends in the number of homelessness entering accommodation without flooring, window co", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rented Housing: Furniture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858926, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96058", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the concerns of frontline homelessness staff who believe that moving homelessness survivors into unf", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rented Housing: Furniture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858924, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he had made of the role of furniture provision in increasing tenancy sustainability and reducing homelessness presentations; and if his department will encourage ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Furniture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858921, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he made of the difference in uptake rates between maternal and infant RSV immunisations when developing the national immunisation programme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Respiratory Syncytial Virus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858920, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of NHS England\u2019s total budget has been allocated to vaccination and immunisation programmes in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vaccination: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858914, "askingMemberId": 5332, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96054", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2025 to Question 94068 on Universal Credit: Veterans, whether the rules have changed since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit: Veterans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858913, "askingMemberId": 5332, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2025 to Question 94068 on Universal Credit: Veterans, if he will set out the reasons for differences in how Armed Forces Pensions and service attributable pensions ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit: Veterans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858890, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96052", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of private finance support for delivering the remainder of the Lower Thames Crossing; and whether she has had discussions with private investors on that subj", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lower Thames Crossing: Private Finance Initiative", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858889, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans she has to use (a) public-private partnership, (b) concessions model, and (c) toll-based financing model for the Lower Thames Crossing; and what options remain under consideration.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lower Thames Crossing: Finance: Private Finance Initiative", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858888, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96050", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans she has to publish regular progress reports detailing (a) expenditure, (b) contractual commitments and (c) updates on the funding position for the Lower Thames Crossing.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lower Thames Crossing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858887, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96049", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the risk of cost escalation in the Lower Thames Crossing project.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lower Thames Crossing: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858886, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96048", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she plans to confirm the remaining funding necessary to complete the Lower Thames Crossing.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lower Thames Crossing: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858885, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will publish a breakdown of all committed public expenditure for the Lower Thames Crossing project to date.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lower Thames Crossing: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858840, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28th November to question 93107, whether his Department will monitor how local authorities spend the Crisis and Resilience Fund; and will the wider essentials section be separa", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crisis and Resilience Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858840", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858839, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96045", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28th November to question 93107, whether the Crisis and Resilience Fund will include an updated management information return to ensure that spend on furniture and white goods ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crisis and Resilience Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858839", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858838, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28th November to question 92800, what information the best practice guide for furniture will provide to tenants about how they can access support with f", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Furniture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858838", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858837, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96043", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28th November to question 92800, whether the best practice guide for furniture provision for all landlords will make specific recommendations to furnish", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Furniture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858837", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858830, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to help increase public confidence in sentencing.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sentencing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858830", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858829, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of sentencing guidelines in preventing reoffending among repeat offenders.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Reoffenders: Sentencing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858829", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858828, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of geographical variations in sentencing outcomes across courts in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sentencing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858828", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858827, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to publish sentencing outcome data broken down by court area.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sentencing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858827", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858825, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the forthcoming integrated national transport strategy will include targets for improving rural bus a) coverage and b) frequency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858825", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858822, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the risks to (a) residents requiring urgent medical treatment and (b) other vulnerable residents when East Tilbury is cut off by level-crossing closures.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Level Crossings: Tilbury", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858822", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858820, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96034", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with Network Rail on whether the isolation of East Tilbury during prolonged barrier closures constitutes a safety risk.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Level Crossings: Tilbury", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858820", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858819, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on safety-risk assessments that consider the consequences for East Tilbury residents being cut off when the level-crossing barriers are down.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Level Crossings: Tilbury", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858819", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858818, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of Network Rail\u2019s compliance with its statutory safety duties in relation to the risk of isolation of East Tilbury when level-crossing barriers remain down for extended periods due ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Level Crossings: Tilbury", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858818", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858817, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with Network Rail on the impact of prolonged closures on (a) community access and (b) local transport while undertaking its statutory duties to ensure safety at East Tilbury Level C", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Level Crossings: Tilbury", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858817", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858816, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Network Rail has provided her with data on (a) barrier-down times, (b) duration of delays or (c) frequency of freight movements at the East Tilbury Level Crossing.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Level Crossings: Tilbury", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858816", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858808, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96029", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if his Department will consider the potential merits of developing a national roadmap with targets for the development of geothermal energy for (a) heat and (b) power generation.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Geothermal Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858808", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858806, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a ring-fenced budget specifically for geothermal projects in the next round of Contract for Difference funding", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Geothermal Power: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858806", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858803, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to improve regulatory support for geothermal energy.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Geothermal Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858803", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858768, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96026", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of electricity demand from AI-related data centres on electricity prices.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Supply: Data Centres", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858768", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858760, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to support humanitarian aid and climate resilience in Somaliland.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Somaliland: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858760", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858758, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to mitigate the mental health impact of proposed changes to settlement routes.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Mental Health", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858757, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to develop a National Integration Strategy for asylum seekers and refugees as part of proposed reforms to the asylum system.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Community Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858756, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether ideas for reforming the Personal Independent Payment assessment criteria and processes requiring additional expenditure will be permitted under the terms of reference of the Timms Review of Pers", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment Assessment Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858755, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Motability Scheme on supporting disabled people into employment and training.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858754, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to remove the work capability assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Work Capability Assessment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858747, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96019", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the recommendations of the Kingdon review of children's hearing services; and if he will set out a timetable for the im", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hearing: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858744, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96018", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of job vacancies in key professions within her Department\u2019s responsibilities, including contractor organisations.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vacancies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858743, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of job vacancies in key professions within her Department\u2019s responsibilities, including contractor organisations.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Vacancies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858742, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96016", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of job vacancies in key professions within his Department\u2019s responsibilities, including contractor organisations.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vacancies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858741, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of job vacancies in key professions within his Department\u2019s responsibilities, including contractor organisations.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vacancies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858739, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96014", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons have humanist pastoral support provided through prison chaplaincy services.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Pastoral Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858738, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96013", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of a centralised Probation service.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Probation Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858737, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96012", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the Motability Scheme on transport barriers experienced by disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858736, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the Motability Foundation on an accessible transition to EVs.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motability: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858735, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Motability Scheme in addressing transport accessibility gaps.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858734, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to ensure that the Cycle to Work scheme supports equitable access for employees, including (a) those with disabilities who require specially adapted bicycles, (b) individuals undertakin", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cycle to Work Scheme: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858724, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96008", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the pay per mile charge for electric vehicles on sales of new i) battery electric cars and ii) plug-in hybrid cars.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858723, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96007", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions she has had with oil and gas companies, industry representatives, supply chains and the energy sector on the impact of the Energy Profits Levy on the availability of investment and skilled workforce", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858722, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made an estimate of the change in the number of jobs in the North Sea oil and gas sector from (a) operator and (b) supply chain companies in each year between 2026 and 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858721, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96005", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she last (a) visited (i) Aberdeen and (ii) Aberdeenshire and (b) met an oil and gas company in (A) Aberdeen and (B) Aberdeenshire in relation to oil and gas activities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858719, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of changes in the level of gas imports from (a) Norway, (b) USA, (c) Qatar and (d) the rest of the world relative to UK domestically produced gas from 20", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Natural Gas: Imports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858701, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "96003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken in response to recent reports of Blue Tongue Disease being detected in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858696, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Budget 2025, what estimate his Department has made of the number of existing Motability Scheme users who may be adversely affected by changes to Motability tax reliefs.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motability: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858695, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96001", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to reduce inflation in the prices of food.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858694, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "96000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Budget 2025, what measures his Department will take to reduce error and fraud in the welfare system by \u00a34.6 billion by 2030-31.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Fraud and Maladministration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858693, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that reforms to the visa system help ensure that UK business can employ talented international workers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Skilled Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858692, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the Budget Statement on 26 November 2025, what estimate his Department has made of how many workers in the Poole constituency will benefit from the planned increase in (a) the Nationa", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Living Wage and Minimum Wage: Poole", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858691, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Budget Statement on 26 November 2025, what estimate his Department has made of how many 16-24 year olds in Poole constituency will have access to the Youth Guarantee and the right ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Schemes: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858690, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95996", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Budget Statement on 26 November 2025, what estimate her Department has made of how many retail, hospitality and leisure businesses in Poole will benefit from lower business rates.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Poole", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858689, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Budget Statement on 26 November 2025, how many of the Government's planned 1.5 million homes will be built in Poole constituency by the end of the Parliamen", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Poole", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858688, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95994", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has been done as to the number of households that are affected by the overall benefit cap, rather than the two child limit.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858687, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95993", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households will be affected by the lifting of the two child benefit cap.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858626, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the initial funding arrangements for Essex's Combined County Authority will be put before Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858517, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95991", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, which industry groups participated in the Warm Homes Plan Stakeholder Panel; what criteria was used for their selection; when the panel has met; and if he will publish the minutes of the meet", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Warm Homes Plan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859011, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer to Question 85849 on Mechanical Thrombectomy: Health Services, what estimate he has made of the time taken for a patient to be transferred from the referring centre to a hosp", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859010, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer to Question 85849 on Mechanical Thrombectomy: Health Services, when he expects people to be able to access thrombectomy services within four hours when needed.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859009, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95988", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer to Question 85849 on Mechanical Thrombectomy: Health Services, how many and what proportion of stroke units are in trusts which offer mechanical thrombectomy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859005, "askingMemberId": 4523, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95987", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what efforts she is taking to make sure that car-sharing is available in London and across the UK, in the context of Zipcar closing its UK operations by the end of the year.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Car Sharing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859004, "askingMemberId": 5043, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to build energetics and munitions factories, particularly in Ayrshire.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ammunition: Factories", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859003, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the inclusion of the book 'Pigeon English' in the English GCSE curriculum in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859001, "askingMemberId": 5221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish details of his Department new private finance model for building neighbourhood health centres and the business case completed for it.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neighbourhood Health Centres: Private Finance Initiative", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859000, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of compelling online trade directories to require tradespeople to verify and display waste carrier licences.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade: Directories", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858999, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95982", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the impact of each exemption from the Household Benefit Cap on (a) the number of households subject to the cap and (b) overall welfare expenditure.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858998, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households with total benefit entitlement above the level of the Household Benefit Cap have entitlement above (a) \u00a330,000, (b) \u00a340,000 and (c) \u00a350,000 per year, or the equivalent weekly and mon", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858997, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95980", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households currently subject to the Household Benefit Cap are living in (a) council housing and (b) housing association accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858996, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of additional households that would become subject to the Household Benefit Cap following the removal of the two-child limit on the Universal Credit C", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858995, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will commission an independent national review into the use of allocation tools in Children\u2019s Continuing Care, with recommendations on legality, safeguarding and transparency, and lay the rep", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Continuing Care: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858994, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many referrals have the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman received in each year since 2015 regarding Children\u2019s Continuing Care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Continuing Care: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858993, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Stage 1 and Stage 2 complaints regarding Children\u2019s Continuing Care were received in each ICB in the last three years, what percentage of those complaints were upheld or partially upheld a", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Continuing Care: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858992, "askingMemberId": 4610, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of maintaining investment in the Global Partnership for Education and Education Cannot Wait in advance of their 2026 replenishments.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Education Cannot Wait and Global Partnership for Education: Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858987, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he Department has made of the potential merits of Ofgem\u2019s pay flexibility business case.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ofgem: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858985, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions his Department has had with the Chief Executive of Ofgem regarding a) the ongoing pay dispute, as well as b) job security at Ofgem.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ofgem: Job Security and Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858964, "askingMemberId": 5053, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95972", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps are being taken to assist British road haulage companies which also operate in the European Union to obtain dual registration of their vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Freight", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858963, "askingMemberId": 5058, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will confirm whether Government supported new homes will be built on known flood plains in Broxtowe.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Broxtowe", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858962, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95970", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of future increases in business rates on the financial sustainability of regional airports and the level of regional air connectivity they are able to provide.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Regional Airports: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858961, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she expects unregulated rail fares to move in line with regulated rail fares this year and over the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858960, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what is the estimated net cost to the public purse of freezing certain regulated rail fares in March 2026 for this and the subsequent five financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858957, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment her Department has made of a) the structural condition of the A180 between the M180 and Immingham Port, b) the adequacy of current life-extending works to support projected increases in H", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "A180: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858956, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95966", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of a) annual levies and monitoring charges associated with environmental mitigation and disposal sites used by UK ports, b) the consistency of fee structures across diffe", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ports: Environment Protection and Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858955, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate his Department has made of a) the average energy cost faced by UK steel producers in the most recent year, b) the equivalent cost faced by producers in France and Germany, and c) the pote", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Iron and Steel: Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858954, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95964", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate the Government has made of a) the annual cost to UK port operators of dredging and disposing of dredged material required to maintain navigational access, b) the proportion of those costs arising ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dredging: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858943, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set a target date for the implementation of a nationwide prostate cancer screening programme for men with a BRCA variant.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858936, "askingMemberId": 5270, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of extending statutory regulation by the Health and Care Professions Council to clinical technologists and sonographers on (a) workforce recruitm", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858933, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95961", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will modify the Business Rates Information Letter (5/2025) sent to English Billing Authorities on 26 November so that that the formula for the calculation of Transitional R", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858925, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment the Government has made of the feasibility of replacing animal testing in the UK with Non-Animal New Approach Methodologies (NAMs); and if this will be reflected in the ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858923, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if she will make an assessment of the potential merit of redirecting existing funding and resources to support the transition to Non-Animal New Approach Methodologies (NAMs) to support ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858922, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether her Department plans to monitor and report on its progress towards phasing out animal testing; and whether industry stakeholders will be involved in assessing the effectiveness ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858918, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of local authorities' ability to deal with increased levels of demand for therapy above the Adoption Support and Special Guardianship Support Fund fair access limit.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Adoption and Special Guardianship Support Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858917, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95956", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2025 to Question 78154 on Adoption and Special Guardianship Support Fund, what assessment her Department has been made of the potential economic impact of funding additional", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858912, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95955", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what behavioural changes have been assumed in modelling revenue projections for the proposed EV mileage charge scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858911, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95954", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the EV mileage charge on the (a) rental and (b) leasing motor vehicle sector, including the implications for (i) fleet turnover and (ii) the supply ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858910, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95953", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the proposed EV mileage charge on (a) electric vehicle residual values and (b) the cost of new electric vehicle finance agreements.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858909, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure ICBs offer routine podiatry surgeries.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Podiatry: Surgery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858908, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95951", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to introduce mandatory method of production labelling on food.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858907, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95950", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will publish the responses to the 2025 consultation on the driving test booking system.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858906, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95949", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of Benefit-in-Kind rates for zero-emission company cars.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Company Cars: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858905, "askingMemberId": 4786, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95948", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that companies operating and earning revenue in the UK do not offshore jobs to reduce tax liabilities; and whether his Department plans to introduce legisl", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Offshoring", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858904, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95947", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the answer of 24 November 2025 to Question 91533 on Brownfield Sites: Biodiversity, whether she plans to consult further on the definition of (a) small and (b) medium sites", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brownfield Sites: Biodiversity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858903, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95946", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the answer of 24 November 2025 to Question 91533 on Brownfield Sites: Biodiversity, if she will ensure adequate Parliamentary scrutiny of that impact assessment before fina", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brownfield Sites: Biodiversity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858902, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95945", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the answer of 24 November 2025 to Question 91533 on Brownfield Sites: Biodiversity, whether the full impact assessment will be published prior to her response to the consul", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brownfield Sites: Biodiversity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858901, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95944", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the answer of 24 November 2025 to Question 91533 on Brownfield Sites: Biodiversity, when the full impact assessment will be published.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Brownfield Sites: Biodiversity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858900, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95943", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to make sites below 0.5 hectares exempt from Biodiversity Net Gain.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858899, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95942", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to answer Question 90914 on NHS: Software.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858898, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95941", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of vehicles used by Government departments are electric; and what recent progress she has made in increasing the use of electric vehicles within the Government fleet.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858895, "askingMemberId": 5220, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95940", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps she is taking to support the development of Quantum Computing, including research at Universities.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Quantum Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858893, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if her Department will issue guidelines to airlines on the treatment of passengers with neurological disabilities, including standardised procedures for fitness-to-fly assessments.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aviation: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858892, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95938", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2025 to Question 67482 on IVF: Greater Manchester, If his Department will have discussions with NHS Greater Manchester following the publication of the Standardisi", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "IVF: Greater Manchester", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858891, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of Royal Mail\u2019s efforts to meet its Quality of Service targets in SK Stockport postcode areas.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Royal Mail: Stockport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858884, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many sustainable aviation fuel plants she expects to be under construction in (a) 2026, (b) 2027, (c) 2028, (d) 2029 and (e) 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aviation: Alternative Fuels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858883, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many sustainable aviation fuel plants are currently under construction.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aviation: Alternative Fuels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858882, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many sustainable aviation fuel plants are currently operational.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aviation: Alternative Fuels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858882", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858881, "askingMemberId": 5058, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether she is taking steps to improve reliability of broadband connection in the Bramcote area.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Broadband: Broxtowe", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858881", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858880, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95932", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to strengthen pathways between (a) school cricket programmes and (b) local community cricket clubs in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cricket: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858880", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858879, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to increase opportunities for (a) children and (b) young people to participate in cricket in schools within the Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cricket: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858879", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858878, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95930", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to strengthen pathways between (a) school netball programmes and (b) local community clubs in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Netball: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858878", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858877, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support schools in (a) upgrading or (b) expanding netball facilities in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Netball: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858877", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858874, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to improve access to racket sports in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tennis: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858874", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858869, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to allocate additional funding to improve (a) parks and (b) recreational facilities in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Recreation Spaces: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858869", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858868, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of current measures to deter antisocial behaviour in car parks in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anti-social Behaviour: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858868", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858867, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities with repeated vandalism impacting the operation of public facilities in Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vandalism: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858867", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858866, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95924", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help local authorities safeguard vulnerable residents from (a) misleading and (b) high-pressure contact relating to (i) housing repairs and", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858866", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858865, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that developers in London allocate 20% of homes for affordable housing.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858865", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858864, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much new burdens funding she plans to allocate for food waste collections; and if she will (a) allocate that funding based on costs incurred by WCAs and (b) apply the New Burdens D", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858864", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858862, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under Secretary for Net Zero during Energy and Net Zero questions on 18 November 2025, on what date he plans to launch the fuel fi", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858862", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858856, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95920", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the transport adaptation strategy will be published.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858856", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858855, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95919", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the Access to Nature Green Paper.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Countryside: Access", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858855", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858854, "askingMemberId": 4777, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Nursing and Midwifery Council on wait times for (a) general cases and (b) cases before the case examiner.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nursing and Midwifery Council: Complaints", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858854", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858836, "askingMemberId": 4521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-10T00:00:00", "uin": "95917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she had made of the effectiveness of the the Merchant Shipping (Watercraft) Order 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858836", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858835, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2025 to Question 82808 on Water Supply: Newton Abbot, what assessment her Department has made of the capacity of Teignbridge District Council to me", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply: Newton Abbot", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858835", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858834, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2025 to Question 82810 on Water Supply: Standards, what further information her Department holds on the reasons for these improvement notices, and ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858834", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858833, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2025 to Question 82811 on Water Supply: Standards, whether she has assessed the adequacy of issuing non-mandatory guidance for private water supply", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858833", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858831, "askingMemberId": 5233, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether her Department plans to review the legal and regulatory framework governing the domestic use of CCTV, with particular reference to protections for individuals whose homes or pri", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "CCTV: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858831", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858821, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what consideration he has made of bringing back the Access to Elected Office Fund for disabled candidates seeking election.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Candidates: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858821", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858815, "askingMemberId": 4601, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether the work of the new Retail and Hospitality Envoy will extend to Scotland; and whether the Envoy will be engaging with representative bodies such as the Scottish Retail Consortium.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry and Retail Trade", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858815", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858814, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95910", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his department has considered the potential merits of mandating a minimum distance of 1km between new Quarries and residential homes or schools.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Quarries: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858814", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858812, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the selection criteria was for the location of the 43 new neighbourhood hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Health Services: Location", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858812", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858811, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95908", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel have had a hearing assessment following operating within an Ajax or Ajax-platform vehicle.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858811", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858809, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Wait 45 policy for ambulance wait times, including on corridor care and patients being looked after in sub-optimal areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858809", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858807, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to reform the compensation formula for maternity negligence compensation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858807", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858805, "askingMemberId": 5227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95905", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure timely chid maintenance payments for single parents.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858805", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858802, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95904", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October to Question 77605 on Health Professions: Regulation, on what date he will publish a consultation on secondary legislation to modernise the General Medical Counc", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Professions: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858802", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858801, "askingMemberId": 4873, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95903", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether financial resources will be made available to charities and voluntary groups organising public events in order for them to comply with the provisions of the Terrorism (Protection Of Premises) ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858801", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858800, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95902", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information her Department holds on the proportion of text redacted in statements provided to hon. Members from opposition parties in advance of the Chancellor\u2019s statement on each Budget day since 1997.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Budgets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858800", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858799, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95901", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish copies of the redacted statements provided to opposition MPs each budget day in advance of the Chancellor\u2019s statement to the House of Commons in each year since 1997.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Budgets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858799", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858798, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of a) simplifying the application process for Bus Passes for disabled passengers, b) removing the time restrictions, and c) ensuring the availability of comp", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858798", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858797, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 14 November 2025, to Question 86767, on Counter-terrorism: expenditure, what was the policy reason for the number of local authorities receiving Prevent funding being reduced", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Counter-terrorism: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858797", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858796, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Home Office and its subcontractor are paying above market rates to hire Houses in Multiple Occupation for asylum accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Multiple Occupation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858796", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858795, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to page 122 of the OBR, Economic and Fiscal Outlook, November 2025, CP1439, 26 November 2025, what is her department\u2019s estimated spending on asylum in 2024-25 and each year of the Spending Rev", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858795", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858794, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much Home Office funding is being provided to the London Borough of Hillingdon in 2025-26 to assist with the costs of asylum seekers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hillingdon", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858794", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858793, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95895", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 13 November 2025, to Question 86773, on Ministers: Council tax, what policy or threshold is used to prevent the occupation of a designated secondary residence as a de facto primary resi", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858793", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858792, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95894", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Office for National Statistics holds data on the number of dwellings in each council tax band by (a) Parliamentary constituency, (b) local authority ward or division or polling district, (c) Lower layer ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858792", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858791, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95893", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 19 November 2025, to Question 89453, on Deputy Prime Minister: Admiralty House, for what reason the second homes premium was billed in July when it had been introduced in from 1 April 2", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deputy Prime Minister: Admiralty House", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858791", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858790, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95892", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, further to paragraph 4.38 of the OBR, Economic and Fiscal Outlook, November 2025, CP1439, 26 November 2025, whether according to information held by HM Treasury, the 10.2 per cent increase in business rate receipts ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858790", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858789, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95891", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Northern Ireland Department of Finance Minister has submitted fiscal devolution plans to her Department in this current Stormont mandate.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Devolution: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858789", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858788, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95890", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, further to paragraph 4.38 of the OBR, Economic and Fiscal Outlook, November 2025, CP1439, 26 November 2025, whether according to information held by HM Treasury, the 10.2 per cent increase in business rate receipts ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858788", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858787, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95889", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has had discussions on further fiscal devolution with Ministers in the Northern Ireland Department of Finance during this current Stormont mandate.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Devolution: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858787", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858786, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95888", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the high value council tax surcharge will be valued by the Valuation Office Agency by the same assumptions and methodology as current council tax, other than the valuation date.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax: Valuation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858786", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858785, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95887", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Budget 2025, HC1492, 26 November 2025, Box 3.H, and Table 4.1, and to the HMT document, Effects of the business rates retail, hospitality and leisure multipliers and high value multiplier of 26", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858785", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858784, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95886", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, further to the publication of the draft Rating List of 26 November 2025, if she will publish the changes in average Rateable Values by (a) local authority and (b) region, compared to the previous Rating List, accord", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858784", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858783, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95885", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Budget 2025, HC1492, 26 November 2025, Table 4.1, what is the evidential basis for the reduction in council tax receipts of (a) -\u00a360 million in 2025-26, (b) -\u00a3120 million in 2026-27, and (c) -\u00a3", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858783", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858782, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to paragraph 5.29 of the OBR, Economic and Fiscal Outlook, November 2025, CP1439, 26 November 2025, if she will provide an annual breakdown of the \u00a315.3 billion cost of asylum accommodation ov", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858782", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858781, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95883", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, further to the written statement of 25 November 2025, HCWS1097, on Devolution and Growth, and further to the Visitor levy policy paper published on 26 November 2025, whether the levy measure will be classed by the G", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visitor Levy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858781", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858780, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95882", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, further to the Autumn Budget 2025, for what reason alcohol duty is being uprated by RPI rather than CPI inflation.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alcoholic Drinks: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858780", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858779, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, further to Table A.5 of the OBR, Economic and Fiscal Outlook, November 2025, CP1439, 26 November 2025, according to information held by HM Government, if he will list the estimat", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858779", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858777, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95880", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, further to paragraph 1.28 of the OBR, Economic and Fiscal Outlook, November 2025, CP1439, 26 November 2025, how the Government intends to finance the cost of the estimated \u00a314 billion of local authority SEND deficit", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858777", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858776, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95879", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate has the Valuation Office Agency made of the number of appeals that will be made against the high value council tax surcharge.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax: Surcharges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858776", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858775, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95878", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Budget 2025, HC1492, 26 November 2025, Box 3.H, and to the HMT document, Effects of the business rates retail, hospitality and leisure multipliers and high value multiplier of 26 November 2025,", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858775", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858772, "askingMemberId": 5105, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employers who (a) pay and (b) do not pay the apprenticeship levy started new learners on apprenticeship programmes in 2024-25.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858772", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858769, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of the Access to Work scheme on the economy and society.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Access to Work Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858769", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858767, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to improve the Access to Work scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Access to Work Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858767", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858766, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a publicly searchable register of individuals convicted of sexual offences.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Violent and Sex Offender Register", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858766", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858765, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95873", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she made of the potential impact of the proposals in the consultation on Earned Settlement on victims of domestic violence before its publication; and what steps she will take to ensur", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: Domestic Abuse", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858765", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858764, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95872", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to enact the socioeconomic measures in the Equality Act 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disadvantaged: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858764", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858762, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many suicides were attended by police in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Suicide", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858762", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858761, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95870", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officer suicides were recorded in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858761", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858749, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with her Cuban counterpart on reports of gender-based violence against women human rights defenders.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858746, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she provides guidance to Train Operating Companies on the declassification of first class portions of services during periods of high demand.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858732, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any organisations have been removed from the list of Armed Forces Covenant signatories due to non-compliance since November 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces Covenant", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858729, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95866", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2025 to Question 92918 on Business Rates, how many business premises (a) have been brought into paying business rates for the first time and (b) will pay more per year in busine", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858728, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95865", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of reducing the RHL multiplier by 20p on the (a) public purse and (b) long term viability of the Retail, Hospitality and Leisure sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858727, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95864", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the reduction of the Retail, Hospitality and Leisure multiplier and the withdrawal of the capped Retail, Hospitality and Leisure Relief scheme on multiple reta", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858726, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95863", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2025 to Question 69409 on Business Rates: Impact Assessments, if she publish sector-specific impact assessments for (a) hospitality, (b) retail and (c) leisure businesses with r", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858725, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95862", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of section 12(1A) and 13 of the Terrorism Act 2000.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Proscribed Organisations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858720, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95861", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support her Department provides to police forces to tackle driving offences linked to (a) alcohol and (b) drug use in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving under Influence: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858718, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the impact of (a) alcohol and (b) drug impairment on road safety in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving under Influence: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858717, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support (a) local authorities and (b) police forces in promoting road safety in Surrey over the festive period.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858715, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of dangerous driving offences in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dangerous Driving: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858714, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95857", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of long-term empty social housing units in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858713, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities with essential repairs in (a) social and (b) council housing in (i) Surrey and (ii) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858712, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95855", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the (a) condition and (b) safety of local authority housing stock in Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Housing: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858711, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how long-term health system cost efficiency is evaluated when decisions are made to decommission locally delivered health programmes in Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858708, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of withdrawing local early-intervention health services on demand for secondary care in Surrey.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858707, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95852", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how locally commissioned health services incorporate peer-reviewed clinical outcomes into decisions on (a) service continuation and (b) withdrawal.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858706, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department provides on changes to locally commissioned health services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858705, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95850", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department issues guidance to local planning authorities on ensuring that public consultation and plan-making processes do not appear (a) biased and (b) predetermined", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858704, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure imported eggs are (a) salmonella free and (b) raised to the same standards as UK produced eggs.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858702, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95848", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to help ensure farmers are not out of pocket for costs incurred under AB12 supplementary feeding for farmland birds.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858700, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will publish a list of the total amount allocated to highways maintenance funding by the department, including one off grants, for the years (a) 2021/22; (b) 2022/23; (c) 2023/24; (d) 2024/25 to Central ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858699, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress has been made on the determination of the future of Birmingham's PFI roads contract.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858698, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95845", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to item 2.1 of the minutes of the 25 April 2025 meeting of the Advisory Panel on Consumer Prices (Stakeholder), what recent progress the Office for National Statistics has made on evaluating the p", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858697, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95844", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress the Office for National Statistics has made on the development of the Household Costs Indices.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cost of Living: Statistics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858686, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle elective care waiting times, including joint replacement surgery, in North Herefordshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Joint Replacements: North Herefordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858685, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to improve time to diagnosis for children and young people with suspected Juvenile Idiopathic Arthritis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arthritis: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858684, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95841", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to ensure the provision of a) surgical hubs and b) community diagnostics centres are aligned with areas with the highest levels of health deprivation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858683, "askingMemberId": 5052, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95840", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his planned timetable is for publishing the forthcoming cross-government homelessness strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858682, "askingMemberId": 5052, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of expanding Housing First provision across England in the forthcoming cross-government homelessness strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing First", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858681, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95838", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she plans to announce how her Department will move to a) 3.0% of GDP and b) 3.5% of GDP on defence spending.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858680, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95837", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the findings of the Office for Budget Responsibility\u2019s Economic Financial Outlook on the potential impact of the new pay-per-mile tax on", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858679, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of trends in the level of the Chinese market share of the electric vehicle market on risks to national security.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858678, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the impact of (a) ownership and (b) investment in Heathrow Airport by Chinese companies.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heathrow Airport: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858677, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95834", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the National security risk posed by (a) ownership and (b) investment by Chinese companies in Heathrow Airport.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heathrow Airport: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858676, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95833", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of equipment of Chinese origin, used by the UK armed forces, which are subject to China\u2019s National Intelligence Law.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "China: Defence Equipment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858675, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95832", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the risk posed by UK armed forces of using 3D printers manufactured by Chinese firm Bambu Labs.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: 3D Printing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858674, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95831", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many portable 3D printers manufactured by Bambi Labs the (a) Royal Navy, (b) British Army and (c) Royal Air Force currently have.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: 3D Printing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858673, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95830", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the impact of the additional \u00a332 billion required to meet the pledge to spend 3.5% of GDP identified by the Office for Budget Responsibility in its 2025 Economic Financial Outlook.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858672, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95829", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the impact of the collapse of negotiations on UK access to the SAFE fund.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858671, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95828", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current book value is of the British Army\u2019s Warrior fleet of vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Warrior Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858670, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95827", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on the sale of HMS Albion.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Albion: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858669, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95826", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current cost of maintaining HMS Albion is.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Albion: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858668, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current book value of HMS Albion is.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Albion", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858667, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment has he made of the (a) immediate and (b) longer-term impact of grounding the SV fleet following the issues encountered during Exercise Titan Storm.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858666, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the \u00a3360m Fishing and Coastal Growth Fund has been invested since the fund was announced.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fishing and Coastal Growth Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858665, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95822", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has she made of the impact of treating 50% of the gain in disposal to trustees of an Employee Ownership Trust as the disposers' chargeable gain for CGT purposes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employee Ownership: Capital Gains Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858665", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858664, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95821", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has he made of the impact of the findings by the study of 1,005 GPs entitled \u201cGeneral practitioners\u2019 adoption of generative artificial intelligence in clinical practice in the UK: A", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858664", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858663, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95820", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the benefits of signing the Security and Defence Partnership in May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "European Union: Military Alliances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858663", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858662, "askingMemberId": 5150, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95819", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the impact on sugar beet producers in England due to the decision to extend tariff-free access for raw cane sugar.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858662", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858661, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95818", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she will determine West Mercia Police's requests for special grant funding for the next financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858661", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858660, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95817", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the outstanding profit share from asylum hotel providers owed to the home office, broken down by provider.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858660", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858659, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what policy he has on match funding raised by charity fundraisers for capital projects that will exclusively benefit the the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858659", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858658, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95815", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children were in poverty in Telford constituency for each year that data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858658", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858657, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95814", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many business pay business rates for each year that data is available in (a) Telford constituency and (b) Telford and Wrekin Local Authority area broken down by type of busin", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858657", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858656, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of young people who have been off-rolled by schools and colleges while awaiting Education, Health and Care Plans in England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858656", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858655, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has been made of the adequacy of multiagency responses to bullying in schools, online and through messaging platforms which disrupt the learning of young people and cause distress and harm.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858655", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858654, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95811", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of education in schools relating to toxic masculinity and misogyny; and what steps her Department is taking to improve culture and behaviours and to promote positive", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858654", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858653, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95810", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the adequacy of advocacy voice and weight given to representations made by family members of patients over 18 years old who are detained or likely to be detained un", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858653", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858652, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the (a) adequacy of support services for families of patients detained or likely to be detained under the Mental Health Act, and (b) benefits of developing a single", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858652", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858651, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95808", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of current inpatient capacity and waiting times for secure mental health placements for individuals detained under the Mental Health Act in (a) England (b) G", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858651", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858636, "askingMemberId": 5197, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95807", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of exempting foster carers from Council Tax in whole or in part.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax: Foster Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858636", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858635, "askingMemberId": 5197, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of increasing the maximum age for post-foster care arrangements to age 25.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foster Care: Care Leavers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858635", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858631, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many visas a) his Department, b) the Information Commissioners Office, c) the Intellectual Property Office, d) the Met Office, e) the UK Space Agency, f) the Advanced Research and I", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858631", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858629, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many visas a) his Department, b) the Legal Services Board and c) the Legal Ombudsman have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Justice: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858629", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858628, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many visas a) HM Land Registry and b) the Architects Registration Board have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858627, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visas a) the Metropolitan Police Service and b) Police Scotland have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858627", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858625, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many visas a) the British Council, b) the Great British China Centre and c) the Westminster Foundation for Democracy have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858625", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858624, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many visas a) the Forestry Commission, b) Ofwat, c) the Centre for Environment, Fisheries and Aquaculture Science, d) the Royal Botanic Gardens Kew, e) the Environment Agency, f) t", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858624", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858623, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95798", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the prevalence of the use of non-disclosure agreements during corporate restructuring in safety-critical sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858623", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858622, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95797", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department are taking to ensure universities offer adequate (a) support and (b) safety provision for visually impaired students.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Visual Impairment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858622", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858621, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95796", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department are taking to help support children with visual impairments in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: Visual Impairment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858621", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858620, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to increase the provision of disability sport in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858619, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95794", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to increase the provision of visually impaired sport in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: Visual Impairment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858619", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858618, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95793", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help increase awareness of good eye care procedure.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ophthalmic Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858617, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of optician services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ophthalmic Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858617", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858616, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many visas a) his Department, b) the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority, c) the National Energy System Operator and d) the Low Carbon Contracts Company have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858616", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858615, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95790", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many visas a) her Department, b) Ofsted, c) the Construction Industry Training Board, d) the Office of the Children's Commissioner and e) the Student Loans Company have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Education: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858614, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95789", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many visas a) his Department, b) the National Army Museum, c) the National Museum of the Royal Navy, d) Sheffield Forgemasters International and e) the Reserve Forces' and Cadets' Associations have sponsored ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858614", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858613, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95788", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visas a) the Department for Culture Media and Sport, b) the Arts Council, c) the National Archives, d) the British Library, e) the British Museum, f) Historic England, g) the Imperial War Mus", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858613", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858612, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95787", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding has been allocated to the Minister for the Union every year since the office was established.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858611, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95786", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many visas a) his Department and b) the Office for National Statistics have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: VIsas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858611", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858610, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95785", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many visas a) his Department, b) the Competition and Markets Authority, c) Companies House, d) the Financial Reporting Council, e) the Trade Remedies Authority, f) the Post Office and g) the Britis", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858609, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95784", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, how many visas the Serious Fraud Office have sponsored since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Attorney General's Office: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858609", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858608, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95783", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has had recent discussions with Anas Sarwar MSP the potential merits of introducing a Scottish visa.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858608", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858599, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of trends in the level of migration of British nationals from the UK on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Emigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858598, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95781", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the reasons for the negative net migration of British nationals from the UK in recent years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Emigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858597, "askingMemberId": 5280, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95780", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue the UK Government anticipates it will obtain from the Sprits Excise Duty on Scotch Whisky, Energy Profits Levy and Agricultural Property Relief from Scotland by the end of this Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858596, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95779", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much and what proportion of funding allocated to AI and semiconductor growth zones will be spent in Wales; and over what timeframe.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Artificial Intelligence and Semiconductors: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858595, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95778", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to provide additional support to devolved governments for public sector pay costs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858594, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the press release entitled What does the Autumn Budget mean for your energy bills?, published on 27 November 2025, what the cost will be of funding the Renewables Obligation", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewables Obligation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858593, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95776", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, which properties will be subject to revaluation by the Valuation Office following the implementation of a High Value Council Tax Surcharge.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax: Valuation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858592, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to freeze travelcard fares in 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Travel Cards: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858591, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an estimate about how much a) income tax, b) National Insurance and c) student loan repayment she expects the average person turning 30 in 2025/26 with a Plan 2 Student Loan to pay by 2029/30.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858590, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 66, paragraph 3.50 of the Budget 2025, for what reason his Department has chosen Tempsford, Leeds South Bank and Crews Hill as its preferred locations for ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "New Towns", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858589, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95772", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of higher-than-forecast inflation and pay growth on devolved governments\u2019 capacity to fund public sector pay settlements.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector: Pay Settlements", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858587, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95771", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the planned \u00a34.9 billion in efficiencies and savings in 2030\u201331 on devolved governments\u2019 budgets.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858586, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95770", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the proposed high-value property surcharge in England will generate Barnett-related consequentials for devolved administrations.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Devolution: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858585, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95769", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish the Treasury\u2019s analysis of how far the uplifts to Welsh Government borrowing and reserve limits restore the real-terms value of those limits since they were set a decade ago.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Welsh Government: Borrowing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858584, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95768", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions she has had with the Welsh Government on the impact of the income tax threshold freeze on Welsh Rates of Income Tax revenues.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Income Tax: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858583, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much the average household in Wales is expected to save on energy bills as a result of the Budget\u2019s Renewables Obligation measure, compared with households in England and Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858582, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95766", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of ending the Energy Company Obligation on private sector investment in home energy efficiency in Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Company Obligation: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858581, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95765", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of planned reductions in departmental spending after 2028 on the Welsh block grant during the next Senedd term.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Expenditure: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858580, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95764", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of front-loaded Barnett consequentials on the Welsh Government\u2019s medium-term financial planning.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Expenditure: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858579, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95763", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, to publish a breakdown of the spending decisions in England that generated the \u00a3508 million of Barnett consequentials for Wales at the 2025 Autumn Budget.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Expenditure: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858578, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95762", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the number of Welsh taxpayers who will be brought into (a) paying income tax, (b) the higher rate band and (c) the additional rate band as a result of the threshold freeze to 2030\u201331.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Income Tax: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858577, "askingMemberId": 5073, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95761", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to publish the review of adult gender services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Dysphoria: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858576, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95760", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies UK\u2019s trust ratings in France, Germany and Italy as reported in the British Council\u2019s Global", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Relations with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858575, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95759", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the findings of the British Council\u2019s Global Perceptions 2025 report on the role of soft power;", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Soft Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858574, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has made an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the findings of the British Council\u2019s Global Perceptions 2025 report on the likelihood of", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business and Trade: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858573, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her strategies on trade, inward investment and international partnerships of the finding in the British Council", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Investment in UK and Overseas Trade", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858572, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95756", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will take steps with the Chancellor of the Exchequer to ensure income generated from speed enforcement is spent on roads maintenance and roads policing.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858572", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858571, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95755", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will update guidance to allow 30mph speed limit repeater signs on roads with street lighting.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858570, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95754", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a formal fast-track process for Disabled Facilities Grant applications for people with progressive and termin", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Facilities Grants: Terminal Illnesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858570", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858569, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission an independent review into her Department's handling, recording and disclosure of absconder data.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858568, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil servants are assigned to locating absconded foreign national offenders and irregular migrants; and whether performance targets are in place for reducing the size of the absconder pool.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders and Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858567, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95751", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of collating information on absconders.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858566, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential public safety risk posed by foreign national offenders and irregular migrants recorded in the total absconder pool; and what risk categories ar", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders and Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858565, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95749", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the foreign national offenders included in the total absconder pool have (a) been re-apprehended, (b) been deported and (c) remain untraceable.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858564, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many irregular migrants in the total absconder pool (a) have been located, (b) have been removed from the UK and (c) remain at large as of the most recent date for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858563, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department provides guidance to officials on matters to draw to the attention of Ministers when drafting answers to Parliamentary Questions.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Parliamentary Questions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858562, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2025 to Question 87832 on RAF Brize Norton: Palestine Action, what was the cost of returning the two damaged aero engines to a serviceable condition.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858561, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she received internal representations on the adequacy of Ministerial replies to Parliamentary Questions on absconders prior to their publication.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858560, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95744", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of Answers to Parliamentary written questions on absconded foreign national offenders and irregular migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders and Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858559, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95743", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she first became aware of the existence of the total absconder pool dataset.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858558, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when total absconder pool figures were first compiled; and how frequently those figures have been updated since.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858557, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95741", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) foreign national offenders and (b) irregular migrants are in the total absconder pool by risk category, criminal history and nationality.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders and Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858556, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2025 to Question 74872 on Deportation, whether this remains the case.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858555, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what evidential basis the Minister of State for Immigration said on 3 September 2025 that her Department does not hold any central record of the requested information on foreign nationals who have ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858554, "askingMemberId": 5251, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what review processes does the Government have in place to assess the adequacy of its trade and investment treaty commitments for the UK-Russia Bilateral Investment Treaty.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: Russia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858553, "askingMemberId": 5251, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment has the Government made of its overall exposure to further potential Investor-State Dispute Settlement cases over sanctions policy on Russia.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: Dispute Resolution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858544, "askingMemberId": 5251, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2025 to Question 89908 on Trade Agreements: Dispute Resolution, what assessment has the Government made of the likely costs of defending the arbitration being brou", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mikhail Fridman", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858539, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, following the recent National Living Wage increase announced in the Budget, what assumptions have been made on future wage differential compression for social care workers currently earning just ab", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Workers: Living Wage", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858538, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95734", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate has been made of the value of the tourism levy by mayoral combined authority area.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tourism: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858537, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the (a) effectiveness of the legal and regulatory framework and (b) use and coverage of facial recognition technology by police forces in England.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Biometrics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858536, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions have taken place with highway authorities in England on the potential impact of yellow box enforcement on congestion and pollution on the road network.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Road Traffic Offences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858535, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the potential impact of average speed cameras on the number of accidents and casualties.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Speed Limits: Cameras", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858534, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the progress in rolling out additional neighbourhood police in (a) England (b) Greater Manchester.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neighbourhood Policing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858533, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95729", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the Office for Budget Responsibility.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Budget Responsibility", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858532, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2025 to Question 77537 on Hotels: Taxation, and with reference to the written statement of 25 November 2025 on Devolution and Growth, HCWS109", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tourism: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858531, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95727", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2025 to Question 93956 on Driving Tests, what is the estimated total cost of the Ministry of Defence charges to the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency for the use of 36 defe", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858530, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95726", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of upgrading and expanding monitoring and stabilisation works on Victorian railway embankments; and whether she plans to publish a timetable for funding for thi", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858529, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95725", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of remote monitoring equipment used to detect landslips on the rail network; and what steps she is taking to improve detection rates.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858528, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95724", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual cost to the public purse is of tax reliefs provided through the Cycle to Work scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cycle to Work Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858525, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children who have an unmet SEND need in England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858524, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what is the current working assumption for the Casey review into adult social care to start and conclude.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Care: Reviews", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858523, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) water pumps and (b) generators his Department disposed of for each year from 2015 to date.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Generators and Water Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858522, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95720", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on community payback services in (a) Greater Manchester (b) Oldham for each year from 2015 to date.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Orders: Greater Manchester", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858521, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95719", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what value and tonnage of UK government aid to Gaza is assessed as (a) delivered, (b) awaiting delivery and (c) not delivered for each month from October 2023 to date.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858520, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of trends in the number of complaints made to Ofgem about solar installation and network feed in as previously exper", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858519, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with Ofwat on its effectiveness at regulating (a) bonuses (b) dividends (c) inter company management charges (d) company debt (e) consumer bills for water ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Companies: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858986, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June to Question 57673 on Military Intelligence, whether his Department has signed any contracts to deliver the Digital Targeting Web since 16 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Military Intelligence: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858982, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Power Improvement Project upgrade on HMS Dauntless.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMS Dauntless: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858981, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November to Question 93042 on Unmanned Air Systems: Manufacturing Industries, whether his Department hold a figure for how many of the 100,000 drones produced this year were made by B", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Unmanned Air Systems: Manufacturing Industries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858977, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Underwater robot could improve pipeline and cable security, published on 9 June 2025, if he will list all contracts placed by his Department with Atlantas", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Atlantas Marine", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858975, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November to Question 93042 on Unmanned Air Systems: Manufacturing Industries, whether his Department keep records of each country of origin that has supplied drones to Ukraine.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ukraine: Unmanned Air Systems", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858974, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95711", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to conduct any future negotiations with his EU counterparts on a UK application to join the EU SAFE fund.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Security Action for Europe", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858973, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95710", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May to Question 52284 on Defence Industrial Joint Council, whether the inaugural DIJC has met since June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence Industrial Joint Council", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858972, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the second round of EU SAFE funding will commence.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Security Action for Europe", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858971, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95708", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the United Kingdom will make a formal application to join the second round of EU SAFE funding.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858970, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the policy paper entitled Security and defence partnership between the European Union and the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, published on 19 May 2025, how many defence con", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858969, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the policy paper entitled Security and defence partnership between the European Union and the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, published on 19 May 2025, if he will state the", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858919, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many mobile launchers will Project Nightfall deliver.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Guided Weapons: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858916, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2025 to Question 93964 on Defence: Contracts, how many of the 1,000 signed contracts are valued below \u00a35 million.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858915, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2025 to Question 93964 on Defence: Contracts, if he will name the (a) six companies with contracts valued above \u00a3500 million and (b) 26 companies with contracts valued betwee", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858876, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he attends meetings between the Prime Minister and the Special Representative on AUKUS.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "AUKUS", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858876", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858875, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95701", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to increase the number of staff supporting the special representative on AUKUS.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "AUKUS", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858875", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858873, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95700", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the special representative on AUKUS employs any full time staff.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "AUKUS", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858873", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858872, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95699", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2025 to Question 34903 on Defence: Procurement, what recent progress he has made on implementing the Defence Small and Medium Enterprise Support Hub.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858872", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858871, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95698", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2025 to Question 52284 on Defence Industrial Joint Council, whether the inaugural DIJC meeting took place in June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence Industrial Joint Council", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858871", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858870, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95697", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September to Question 70699 on UK Defence and Security Exports, where UK Defence and Security Exports is based.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Defence and Security Exports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858870", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858552, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department is taking steps with the Department for Transport to improve emissions monitoring and enforcement mechanisms to prevent future breaches of vehicle emissions law.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Exhaust Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858551, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95695", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential lessons learned from other countries on tackling historic diesel emissions; and how this informs the UK\u2019s approach to integrating tran", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diesel Vehicles: Exhaust Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858550, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department plans to include measures within future energy and climate plans to offset or remediate the environmental and public-health impacts of illegally high vehicle emissions.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Exhaust Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858549, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95693", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential health and social impacts of illegal vehicle emissions on communities living in areas that already breach air-quality standards; and how those findings i", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Exhaust Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858548, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95692", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions he has held with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs and the Secretary of State for Transport regarding cross-government action to address illegal ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Exhaust Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858547, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95691", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that emissions from non-compliant diesel vehicles are fully accounted for in the modelling and monitoring underpinning the UK\u2019s Net Zero Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diesel Vehicles: Exhaust Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858546, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95690", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate her Department has made of the potential impact of non-compliant diesel vehicles on the UK\u2019s ability to meet its legally binding carbon budgets and net-zero targets.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diesel Vehicles: Exhaust Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858545, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95689", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the contribution of illegally high vehicle emissions arising from the use of defeat devices to overall UK nitrogen oxide and greenhouse gas emissions levels.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Exhaust Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858810, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95688", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the application of the new individual earnings requirement applies to spouses of UK citizens who are retired, carers, or stay-at-home parents.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Married People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858810", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858634, "askingMemberId": 4491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95687", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent progress his Department has made towards publishing the details of how funding will be allocated to different schemes under the Warm Homes Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Warm Homes Plan: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858634", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858633, "askingMemberId": 4491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95686", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent progress his Department has made towards publishing the details of the Warm Homes Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Warm Homes Plan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858633", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858748, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95685", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with the (a) Mayor of London, (b) Greater London Authority and (c) Metropolitan Police on the decision to cancel the farmers\u2019 tractor protest in", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Demonstrations: Whitehall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858745, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95684", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the notice period given to organisers of the farming protest on 26 November 2025 of the cancellation of that protest.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Demonstrations: Whitehall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858745", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858832, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with international partners on protecting women and girls in El Fasher, Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858832", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858543, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether protections against assaults for retail workers in the Crime and Policing Bill will apply to public transport workers involved in the retail of (a) refreshments and (b) rail products and ticke", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858542, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with the Rail Delivery Group, Network Rail and British Transport Police on the potential merits of a standalone offence of assaulting a public transport worker.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Transport: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858541, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95680", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of a standalone offence of assaulting a public transport worker.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858540, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of legal protections against assaults at work for public transport workers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858527, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95678", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to ensure family hubs are accessible for adoptive and kinship families.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858526, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95677", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October to Question 78154, how much of the \u00a3500 million allocated to local authorities for Family Help services is being allocated to help adoptive and kinship families with post pl", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858518, "askingMemberId": 4471, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of patient safety risks, including those relating to malnutrition, among people with severe and very severe ME/CFS in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Malnutrition: Chronic Fatigue Syndrome", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858966, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to support North East Lincolnshire Council to complete the long-overdue repairs and re-open Corporation Bridge in Great Grimsby.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858813, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95674", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of potential merits of introducing routine finger-prick blood glucose testing or urine testing for children who display one or more recognised symptoms of Type 1 diabete", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858813", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858774, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of early years SEND support capacity in North East Lincolnshire; and what support her Department is providing to ensure early identification and intervention for children age", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: North East Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858774", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858773, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that children referred for (a) neurodevelopmental and (b) paediatric assessment continue to receive care during transitions between (i) services and (i", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neurodiversity: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858773", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858763, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has set performance targets for the Child Maintenance Service on (a) time to initial calculation, (b) time to enforcement following non payment, and (c) customer satisfaction.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858763", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858640, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is for initial maintenance calculations; and what the main causes of delay in making those calculations are.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858640", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858639, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Maintenance Service calculations were revised following (a) Mandatory Reconsideration and (b) appeal in each of the last five years; and what the total value of revised liabilities was in", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858639", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858638, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) mandatory reconsiderations and (b) appeals have been requested in each of the last five years; and what is the average time it takes the Child Maintenance Service to review these requests.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858638", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858637, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average and maximum response times are for the Child Maintenance Service providing parents with full statements and breakdowns of maintenance calculations and variations on request.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858637", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858950, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95666", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will review energy support and taxation policy for energy-intensive industries such as quarrying to ensure fair treatment compared with high-carbon sectors like steel and glass.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858948, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95665", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the impact of energy costs and industrial tariffs on small and medium-sized enterprises in the UK stone and quarrying industry.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Quarrying: Small Businesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858946, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95664", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the forthcoming Planning and Infrastructure Bill will include measures to support the use of low-carbon, natural building materials.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Construction: Materials", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858944, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95663", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with the construction industry on planning barriers and standards affecting the use of natural materials such as stone in new developments.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Construction: Materials", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858941, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95662", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of heritage skills training to support employment and regeneration in rural and post-industrial areas.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crafts: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858935, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95661", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to promote heritage craft and stonemasonry apprenticeships as part of the wider skills and construction workforce strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crafts: Apprentices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858934, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of the potential economic impact of foreign government subsidies on the competitiveness of UK natural stone producers; and whether the Government plans to introduce target", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stone: Trade Competitiveness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858932, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95659", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will review public procurement guidance to ensure that locally and sustainably sourced building materials are prioritised in public projects.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858931, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the contribution of natural stone and other low-carbon materials to reducing embodied carbon in the UK construction sector.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Construction: Stone", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858861, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what data she holds on the use of Withdrawal of Implied Permission notices by train operating companies.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858861", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858860, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to support the development of a railway-wide Withdrawal of Implied Permission notice.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858860", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858859, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the sanction of a Withdrawal of Implied Permission notice by one Train Operating Company is confined to the services of the train operating company applying that sanction.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858859", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858858, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which train companies contracted to her Department utilise Withdrawal of Implied Permission notices.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858858", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858857, "askingMemberId": 4396, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance she has given to train companies contracted to her Department on the usage of Withdrawal of Implied Permission notices.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858857", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858853, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95652", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment they have made of the impact of vetting delays on (a) recruitment and (b) project delivery across government departments and national security agencies.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Vetting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858853", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858852, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95651", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what is the most recent estimate of (a) the headcount size of the Government Communication Service and (b) staff who work in communications functions in the Civil Service who are not GCS.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Communications", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858852", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858851, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95650", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to his Department's press release entitled Civil Service staff networks to only meet outside working hours and have all events signed off by senior managers, published on 23 September 2025 if he will pl", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858851", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858850, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95649", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Office for National Statistics has made an assessment of the adequacy of GDP deflation forecasts.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inflation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858850", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858849, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95648", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will ensure that direct ministerial appointments publish a declaration of interests on gov.uk.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Appointments: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858849", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858848, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95647", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 23 September 2025 to Question 75722 on Government Departments: Advertising, if he will publish equivalent data for spending on (a) hard copy advertising, (b) public relations and (c) ma", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Advertising", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858848", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858847, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95646", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are employed by UK Security Vetting by (a) permanent civil servants, (b) fixed-term appointees and (c) contingent labour.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "United Kingdom Security Vetting: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858847", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858846, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95645", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 2 September 2025 to Question 69278 Cabinet Office: Electronic Purchasing Card Solution, if he will itemise the \u00a37,395 spent.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Electronic Purchasing Card Solution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858846", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858845, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95644", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 10 October 2025 to Question 73728 on Cabinet Office: OCS Group, whether the Social Value Outcome and Diversity reports produced by OCS are retained by his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: OCS Group", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858845", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858844, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95643", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has issued guidance on civil servants claiming trade union facility time and diversity network time.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Facilities Agreements", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858844", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858843, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95642", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 3 September 2025, to Question 70509, on Government Departments: Buildings, what is the current ownership and freehold, leasehold or rental status, of the Department for Education buildi", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Education: Buildings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858843", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858842, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95641", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the Permanent Secretary model contract released under FOI reference FOI2025/09712 of September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Permanent Secretaries: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858842", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858841, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95640", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on severance payments to outgoing Cabinet Secretaries and Permanent Secretaries not provided for in the model contract.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Senior Civil Servants: Redundancy Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858841", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858771, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95639", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 24 October 2025 to Question 82675 on Civil Service: Redundancy, which public body collated and provided that data to the National Audit Office.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service: Redundancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858771", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858770, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95638", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the answer of 28 October 2025 to Question HL10808 on Official Residences, how long the other residences have been unoccupied.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Official Residences: Empty Property", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858770", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858978, "askingMemberId": 4382, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her department (a) conducted a review of the reliability of its data on seabed habitats in Marine Protected Areas (MPAs) before announcing proposed fisheries management measure", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marine Protected Areas: Seabed", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858976, "askingMemberId": 4382, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her department will conduct a full benthic audit of seabed habitats in the 41 Stage 3 Marine Protected Areas before designating new fisheries management measures.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marine Protected Areas: Seabed", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858968, "askingMemberId": 4382, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95635", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has made and assessment of the potential merits of re-auditing seabed habitats in Marine Protected Areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marine Protected Areas: Seabed", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858979, "askingMemberId": 4371, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95634", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her Iranian counterpart concerning the recent detention of Afghan Christian, Teymur Hosseini; and what diplomatic steps she is taking", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858863, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "95633", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the assurance processes are under which the Post Opening Project Evaluation (POPE) of Major Schemes are conducted.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858863", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858804, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95632", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether the Government will be represented at the Gaza Reconstruction Conference in Egypt and at what ministerial level the UK will be represented; and whether the Government", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestine: Reconstruction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858804", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858716, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95631", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the UN Human Rights Council\u2019s recent urgent call for an inquiry into violations in El Fasher, S", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Human Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858588, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will include provisions in the forthcoming National Development Management Policies to increase the number of stepping stone housing models across local authority areas.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness: Temporary Accommodation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858607, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of changes in the diagnosis rates of mental health conditions and neurodivergence in England in the last five years", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health and Neurodiversity: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858606, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95628", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what evidence his Department has received on the potential over-diagnosis of mental health conditions and neurodivergence.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health and Neurodiversity: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858606", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858605, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the mental health and neurodivergence sectors on over-diagnosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health and Neurodiversity: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858604, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether organisations in the mental health sector will be asked to contribute evidence to the Department\u2019s review into the over-diagnosis of mental health conditions and neurodivergence.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health and Neurodiversity: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858603, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to consult stakeholders in the mental health and neurodivergence sectors as part of its review into over-diagnosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health and Neurodiversity: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858602, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the terms of reference for the Department\u2019s review into the prevalence and potential over-diagnosis of mental health conditions and neurodivergence.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health and Neurodiversity: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858601, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the proposed scope and timetable for his Department\u2019s review into the prevalence of the potential over-diagnosis of mental health conditions and neurodivergence.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health and Neurodiversity: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858600, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is undertaking a review into the prevalence of the over-diagnosis of mental health conditions and neurodivergence.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health and Neurodiversity: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858991, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he expects to complete his review of stakeholder feedback submitted in April 2025 on the Part IX re-categorisation process for Waves 1 to 4, and when updates will be shared with the Drug Tarif", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drugs and Medical Equipment: Prescriptions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858990, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to update the Wave 1 Part IX categorisation published by the NHS Business Services Authority: and what mechanisms are in place for the Drug Tariff Committee and suppliers to provide i", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drugs and Medical Equipment: Prescriptions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858778, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her Iranian counterpart on the recent detention of Baha\u2019i, Aminollah Koushkbaghi; and what diplomatic steps she is taking to ensure h", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aminollah Koushkbaghi", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858778", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858930, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95618", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the reliability of Northern's services on the East Durham coastline from (a) Seaham (b) Horden stations.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Northern Trains: East Durham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858897, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95617", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of planned double duty increases on tobacco products on inflation.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tobacco: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858896, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95616", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason tobacco duty increased above the rate of inflation in the Autumn Budget 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tobacco: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858894, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95615", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of registering people involved in the distribution and sale of excise goods in a national scheme administered by HMRC.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Imports: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1859006, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has had discussions with Stellantis on the (a) recall and (b) check of (i) Citro\u00ebn and (ii) DS Automobiles branded cars potentially affected by a airbag safety fault.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1859006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858703, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95612", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the difference in annual net income during 2027 for people whose total gross income is \u00a313,000 composed of (a) only the new State Pension, and (b) a basic State Pension plus a personal ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858984, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95611", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will estimate the number of households with a non-working smart meter in the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Meters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858983, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95610", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much the Boiler Upgrade Scheme paid out for heat pumps in the West Midlands over the past year.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Boiler Upgrade Scheme: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858630, "askingMemberId": 429, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "95609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what amount of financial savings the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army, and (c) Royal Air Force have been asked to make in financial years (i) 2025-26 and (ii) 2026-27.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858630", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858759, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was of the use of taxis by asylum seekers in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Taxis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858740, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any new veteran support centres will be located in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans Support Centres: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858733, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95606", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve integration between NHS services and social care provision in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services and  Social Services: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858710, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95605", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve maternity and neonatal care for people in (a) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Maternity Services and Baby Care Units: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858709, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support police forces in tackling shoplifting in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shoplifting: South Holland and the Deepings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858953, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95603", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures she is taking to ensure the national curriculum equips children with the skills they will need with the increasing influence of AI.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Artificial Intelligence: Curriculum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858951, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95602", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures she is taking to improve access in schools to music, sport, art and drama for all children.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Arts and Sports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858947, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95601", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps her department is taking to minimise barriers for international firms to invest in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Investment in UK", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858945, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95600", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to support veterans into suitable employment.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858942, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what progress his Department is making on negotiating free-trade agreements.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858940, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to support the hospitality sector in North East Somerset and Hanham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry: North East Somerset and Hanham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858939, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps she is taking to support the life sciences sector.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Life Sciences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858938, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what progress he has made on supporting small and medium-sized businesses in North East Somerset and Hanham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: North East Somerset and Hanham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858937, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress she has made on increasing skills via apprenticeships, technical colleges and regional training programmes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices and Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858641, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency last reviewed the driving test questions relating to (a) horse riders (b) cyclists and (c) motorcyclists.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858641", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858650, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, What assessment she has made of the triggers for violence perpetrated on the rail network.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858650", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858649, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she requires the train companies contracted to her Department to include trade union health and safety representatives in post violent incident activity including safety inspections, violence at work po", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858649", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858648, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, What assessment she has made of the sharing of violence at work data with trade unions by the train companies contracted to her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858648", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858647, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, What assessment has she made of the adequacy of reporting procedures for workplace violence at the train companies contracted to her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858647", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858646, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, What instructions has she given to the train companies contracted to her Department on the consideration of violence at work as part of workplace stress risk assessments.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858646", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858645, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, What instructions has she given to the train companies contracted to her Department on the need to undertake violence at work risk assessments.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858645", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858644, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, What assessment has she made of the training provided to frontline rail workers on dealing with conflict at work.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858644", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858643, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, What instruction she has given to the train companies contracted to her Department on the lone working of rail staff and the impact on staff safety and security.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858643", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858642, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, What assessment has been made of the adequacy of training in the use of body worn cameras for rail staff on Train companies contracted to her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858642", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858753, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95584", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to help tackle deforestation, air pollution and community health impacts linked to imported biomass supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Biofuels: Supply Chains", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858752, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95583", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to ensure that new contracts for biomass do not lead to long-term reliance on imported feedstocks.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Biofuels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858751, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95582", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether biomass subsidies are compatible with the recommendations of the Independent Review of the UK's Greenhouse Gas Removal Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Biofuels: Subsidies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858750, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95581", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to ensure transparency over contract terms agreed with Lynemouth under new low-carbon dispatchable power arrangements.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lynemouth Power Station: Biofuels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858731, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the Health and Safety Executive no longer assesses a risk of continuing harm to staff from wood dust exposure at Drax Power Station.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drax Power Station: Timber", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1858730, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "95579", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, pursuant to the answer of 21 November 2025 to question 90099, what his evidential basis is for Drax's policy of not sourcing material directly from old growth areas; and whether his Departmen", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drax Power Station: Timber", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1858730", "method": "GET"}]}]